pressures
圧力
GT
GT
retreat
退却
OK
OK
Go
行く
come tell us about this
このことについて話しに来てください
See the world from your phone
携帯電話から世界を見る
i think we are now
私たちは今だと思います
indeed every day
本当に毎日
Everyone can't live without their mobile phone
おそらく誰もが携帯電話なしでは生きていけないでしょう
So this topic should be of interest to many people.
したがって、このトピックは多くの人にとって興味深いものとなるはずです。
Interest also took the opportunity to learn
興味を持って学ぶ機会も得ました
including me
私も含めて
We all say that the older the person, the less likely he is to use the phone
高齢になればなるほど、電話を使用する可能性が低くなると誰もが言います。
I am one of them so today also
私もその一人なので今日も
hope to wait
待ちたいと思っています
become
なる
slightly to the phone
少し電話に向かって
know a little
少し知っています
Let me briefly introduce our keynote speaker today
本日の基調講演者を簡単に紹介させていただきます
learning experience
学習経験
that he is
彼がそうだということ
Department of Information Engineering, National Taiwan University in 1986
1986年に国立台湾大学情報工学科卒業
BS
BS
after graduation
卒業後
went
行った
Texas A&M
テキサスA&M
Texas Austin
テキサス州オースティン
Get a master's and a doctorate in computer science
コンピューターサイエンスの修士号と博士号を取得する
1990 to 1990 and 1994 respectively
それぞれ1990年から1990年と1994年
After he came back, he served in the Information Department of National Taiwan University.
帰国後は国立台湾大学情報学部に勤務。
At present, besides being a member of this hospital, he is also
現在、彼はこの病院の一員であると同時に、
Director of Capital Innovation Center
キャピタルイノベーションセンター所長
Also Professor of Peace at National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学平和教授も務める
Dr. Guo is also currently serving as the vice-chairman of ACM SIGUP
Guo 博士は現在、ACM SIGUP の副会長も務めています。
Talk to the executive member of the ITREPORTE timely system technical committee
ITREPORTEタイムリーシステム技術委員会の執行メンバーと話す
It is the most important executive committee member in the Executive Academy
エグゼクティブアカデミーの最も重要な実行委員です
Also served as editor-in-chief and editor-in-chief of many international academic journals
多くの国際学術誌の編集長、編集長も歴任。
Dr. Guo is Kaida and our peace
郭博士はカイダであり、私たちの平和です
He is currently a Fellow of ACM and a Fellow of IEEE
現在、ACM のフェローおよび IEEE のフェローを務めています。
His works have also won the TECO Award
彼の作品はTECO賞も受賞しています
It is also regarded as an engineering award in China
中国では技術賞ともみなされる
Also received three National Science Council Dismissal Awards
全米学術会議解雇賞も3回受賞
This is the predecessor of the Ministry of Science and Technology
これが科学技術省の前身です。
Also won the Top Ten Contact Youth of the Republic of China
中華民国トップ10コンタクトユース賞も受賞
Academia Sinica Young Scholar Book Award
中央研究院若い学術図書賞
I forgot he's actually the youngest of all our directors
忘れていましたが、実は彼は当社の取締役の中で最年少です
Society of Electrical Engineers Contact Electrical Engineering Professor Award
電気学会 お問い合わせ 電気工学教授賞
And too big a teaching award, etc.
そして大きすぎる教育賞など。
I won't waste your time anymore
もうあなたの時間を無駄にしません
we are also very much looking forward to
私たちもとても楽しみにしています
Can get a little more information in the future
今後、もう少し詳しい情報が得られるかもしれません
Thanks
ありがとう
please
お願いします
Thank you very very much Vice President
副社長、本当にありがとうございました
When the vice president asked me to talk about a topic?
副大統領が私にあるテーマについて話すように頼んだとき?
I just thought of what to say best
何を言うのが一番良いか考えただけ
Because the phone is always on
電話は常にオンになっているため、
I just thought that this machine is in my hand, hope is endless
このマシンが私の手の中にあると思った、希望は無限だ
OK
OK
So let’s talk about viewing the world from your mobile phone
それでは、携帯電話から世界を見ることについて話しましょう
Well, this topic
さて、この話題
I was once in a popular science speech
私はかつて人気の科学講演に参加したことがあります
slightly mentioned
わずかに言及された
If you have seen
見たことがあるなら
Take what you have heard as a review
聞いたことを復習として取り入れてください
Of course everyone has a cell phone
もちろん誰もが携帯電話を持っています
Everyone says why smartphones are smart
スマートフォンが賢い理由は誰もが言う
people often ask this question
人々はよくこの質問をします
So what's the difference with the previous mobile phone?
では、以前の携帯電話と何が違うのでしょうか？
Then I want to look at it from this angle
じゃあこの角度から見てみたい
See the world from your phone
携帯電話から世界を見る
If you look at the world from your mobile phone
携帯電話から世界を見てみると
I'm bound to talk about the phone and what's around it
電話とその周りのすべてについて話さなければなりません
so therefore
だからだから
Here I choose to speak with Android
ここでは Android と話すことを選択します
Because Android has the highest market share
Android が最も高い市場シェアを持っているため
80% of all mobile phones equals 82%
携帯電話全体の 80% は 82% に相当します
are so-called Android phones
いわゆるAndroidスマートフォンです
So from the perspective of Android
Android の観点から見ると
So let's talk about Android and its environment
それでは、Android とその環境について話しましょう
Of course when it comes to this
もちろんこうなったら
we'll look back
私たちは振り返ってみましょう
Why is it called a smartphone
なぜスマートフォンと呼ばれるのか
isn't it just a mobile phone
携帯電話だけじゃないですか
let's just call
電話してみましょう
Why is it called a smartphone
なぜスマートフォンと呼ばれるのか
Remember everyone will find out
誰もが知ることになるだろうということを忘れないでください
I actually do a lot of things on my phone
実はスマホでいろんなことをしているんです
That seems to answer all kinds of questions I have.
それは私のあらゆる種類の質問に答えてくれるようです。
so i think it's a smartphone
だからスマホだと思う
In that case maybe we should see
その場合は見てみるといいかもしれません
This so-called smart phone
このいわゆるスマートフォン
what's behind
後ろに何があるのか
can bring us these wisdom
私たちにこれらの知恵をもたらすことができます
Of course everyone said
もちろん誰もが言いました
what if that's the case
それが事実ならどうするか
I should be more and more established
どんどん定着していけばいいのに
or use my phone
または私の電話を使用してください
Everything is on my phone
すべては私の携帯電話にあります
like me now
今の私のように
I listen to music on my phone
携帯電話で音楽を聴きます
What about taking pictures?
写真を撮るのはどうですか？
In fact, most of the photos I took are also on my mobile phone.
実際、私が撮った写真のほとんどは携帯電話にもあります。
i think most of you here
ここにいる皆さんのほとんどがそうだと思います
They must be taking pictures with their cell phones.
彼らは携帯電話で写真を撮っているに違いありません。
well maybe so
まあそうかもしれない
I am like this
私はこんな感じです
I stopped buying cameras many years ago
何年も前にカメラを買わなくなった
because my cell phone works fine
私の携帯電話は正常に動作するので
After I finished taking the photo, he uploaded it directly to the Internet.
私が写真を撮り終わると、彼はそれをインターネットに直接アップロードしました。
and it's easy to share with others
他の人と共有するのも簡単です
I can use that
それは使えるよ
these different messaging programs
これらのさまざまなメッセージング プログラム
I can send it to anyone
誰にでも送れます
perfectly worked
完璧に機能しました
Of course, after Shu Bodong got on the phone
もちろんShu Bodongが電話に出た後
you should ask a question
質問したほうがいいですよ
Will he be like my personal computer one day
いつか彼は私のパーソナルコンピュータのようになるだろうか
There is a virus in
中にウイルスが入っています
one day when you open
ある日、あなたが開いたとき
he appears blue
彼は青く見える
you can't make phone calls
電話をかけることはできません
what to do
何をすべきか
or
また
I put all my stuff on my phone
すべての持ち物を携帯電話に入れています
one day he told you
ある日彼はあなたに言った
Sorry, the address book is gone
ごめんなさい、アドレス帳が消えてしまいました
do you feel panicked
パニックを感じていますか
I think everyone has this problem
誰もがこの悩みを抱えていると思います
that's not all
それがすべてではありません
When Shu Bodong got on the phone
シュー・ボドンが電話に出たとき
Everyone is like me, I carry my mobile phone with me every day
誰もが私と同じで、私は毎日携帯電話を持ち歩きます
Every morning when I go out without my mobile phone
毎朝携帯電話を持たずに外出するとき
I feel weird today
今日は変な気分です
That's not true, everyone
そんなことないよ、みんな
you will find many things
あなたはたくさんのことを見つけるでしょう
Began to connect more and more with the mobile phone
携帯電話でどんどんつながり始めた
why do you feel a little flustered
なぜ少し慌てているのですか
if you do not have
持っていない場合
go out without a mobile phone
携帯電話を持たずに外出する
now because
今だから
This is how other people contact you
他の人があなたに連絡する方法は次のとおりです
You use these methods to quickly send some text messages to people
これらのメソッドを使用して、テキスト メッセージを人々にすばやく送信します。
so convenient
とても便利です
Slowly you may find that
徐々にそれがわかるかもしれません
You will become more and more dependent on your mobile phone
携帯電話にますます依存するようになる
Why
なぜ
Everyone has heard of the Internet of Things, right?
誰もがモノのインターネットについて聞いたことがあるでしょう?
Internet of Everything
すべてのインターネット
What things will be connected to the Internet?
どのようなものがインターネットに接続されるようになるのでしょうか?
In fact, you can imagine the future
実は未来を想像することもできる
your glasses
あなたのメガネ
It's like the Google glasses you see, right?
Google メガネのようなものですよね。
Many people will wear all kinds of things in the future
将来、多くの人があらゆる種類のものを着るでしょう
always like your current logger
常に現在のロガーのように
There are still many things you will hang on your body in the future
これからも体にぶら下げるものがたくさんあります
even wear it
それを着ても
At this time, you will find that you don’t leave your mobile phone anymore
この時点で、もう携帯電話を手放していないことに気づくでしょう
because everything is connected
すべてはつながっているから
after everything is connected
すべてがつながった後
I ask you
私は尋ねる
Would you like to pay a phone bill per device
デバイスごとに電話料金を支払いますか?
of course not right
もちろん正しくありません
In the end, everything can be sent to your mobile phone
最終的にはすべてを携帯電話に送信できます
So when you don't have your phone
だから、携帯電話を持っていないときは、
I believe you will be more anxious
もっと不安になると思います
ok there is no way
わかりました、方法はありません
because
なぜなら
This is some further development
これはさらなる発展です
So I want to take this opportunity today
そこで今日はこの機会を利用したいと思います
We watched it all the way from the phone
ずっとスマホから見ていました
See what this idea of ​​the future of IoT could look like
IoT の未来に関するこのアイデアがどのようなものになるかを見てみましょう
Everyone look at your phone
みんなあなたの携帯電話を見てください
Do you guys only have a cell phone to call?
皆さんは携帯電話しか持っていないんですか？
Believers raise hands
信者たちが手を挙げる
No, no, no one believes, right?
いやいや、誰も信じてないですよね？
Can a computer make phone calls before?
コンピューターは以前から電話をかけることができましたか?
The computer can't make phone calls, right?
パソコンでは電話はかけられませんよね？
Since the beginning of the so-called video telephony
いわゆるテレビ電話の始まりから
The computer starts to make phone calls
コンピューターが電話をかけ始める
then you find one thing
それからあなたは一つのことを見つけます
Computers used to do these calculations and data processing for me
以前はコンピューターがこれらの計算とデータ処理を行ってくれました
i can surf the internet i can shop
インターネットサーフィンもできますし、買い物もできます
can play electric toys
電動おもちゃで遊ぶことができます
Mobile phones seem to be able to do this now.
今では携帯電話でもこれができるようです。
So therefore you start to have an idea
したがって、あなたはアイデアを持ち始めます
The world of mobile phones and computers has actually begun to integrate
携帯電話とコンピュータの世界は実際に統合され始めています
these two things put together
これら 2 つのことを合わせて
In the past, we applied to the telecom company for a door number
以前、通信会社にドア番号を申請しました。
receive his telecommunications service
彼の電気通信サービスを受ける
And these telecommunications services from
そして、これらの電気通信サービスは、
From domestic calls, long-distance calls, international calls, transferred conference calls, etc.
国内電話、長距離電話、国際電話、転送電話会議など。
These are the services provided by the telecommunications company to you.
これらは通信会社がお客様に提供するサービスです。
what about now you start to think about it
今から考え始めたらどうですか？
seems different
違うようです
What about my phone company, whether it's Chunghwa Telecom or Taiwan Mobile?
私の電話会社は中華電信か台湾移動ですか?
It seems that it is not the same as before
どうやら以前と同じではないようです
not like a phone company
電話会社とは違います
Fast glasses that function as smartphones
スマートフォンとしても機能するファストグラス
Internet access has become very convenient
インターネット接続がとても便利になりました
you also noticed one thing
あなたも一つ気づいたことがある
It seems that the world of the Internet and the world of telecommunications have begun to merge
インターネットの世界と通信の世界が融合し始めているようです
The formerly so-called world of telecommunications
以前所謂的電信的世界
It's as if we call the phone company that provides our service
サービスを提供する電話会社に電話するようなものです
It is they who provide us with the contact method of telecommunications
私たちに電気通信という通信手段を提供しているのは彼らです
The Internet used to belong to our computers only.
インターネットはかつて私たちのコンピューターだけのものでした。
Now what about these telecommunications companies that provide you with Internet access
では、インターネット アクセスを提供する通信会社はどうでしょうか。
It also provides your telecommunications services from now on
今後は通信サービスも提供します
Then you will find that there are some so-called
そうすれば、いわゆるものがいくつかあることがわかります。
This Internet company, he also started a telecommunications company business
このインターネット会社、通信会社の事業も始めた
Of course this means
もちろんこれはつまり
what's starting to come together
何がまとまり始めているのか
In addition, your mobile phone is no longer a phone call.
さらに、携帯電話は電話ではなくなります。
Think about how many things you do on your phone
携帯電話でどれだけのことをしているかを考えてみましょう
let me ask you first
まず聞いてみましょう
Everyone, you want to know the weather this morning
みなさん、今朝の天気を知りたいですよね？
Or if it rains, how many people check the computer
あるいは、雨が降ったら、何人がコンピューターをチェックするでしょうか
How many people look at their mobile phones
携帯電話を見ている人は何人いますか
I look at my phone OK
携帯電話を見たらOKです
Many people look at their phones, right?
スマホを見ている人も多いですよね？
Because it's so convenient that everything is on top
全部上にあると便利だから
OK there are all kinds of software on it
OK、あらゆる種類のソフトウェアが入っています
You can download and use
ダウンロードして使用できます
In the past you had to find a software
以前はソフトウェアを探す必要がありました
Is it troublesome to install it on your computer?
パソコンにインストールするのは面倒ですか？
You need someone to pretend for you, right?
あなたの代わりに誰かが必要ですよね？
now you have an android phone
今あなたはアンドロイド携帯電話を持っています
or you have an iPhone
またはiPhoneをお持ちですか
you need to install new software
新しいソフトウェアをインストールする必要があります
Many of you may come to his
多くの人が彼のところに来るかもしれません
His so-called market
彼のいわゆるマーケット
or play a different site
または別のサイトで再生する
directly downloaded
直接ダウンロードされた
one click and it will come down
ワンクリックで降りてきます
So actually
それで実際には
Everything seems to be very, very convenient
すべてがとてもとても便利に思えます
Everything starts to concentrate on your phone
すべてがスマートフォンに集中し始める
Extremely convenient to use
非常に使いやすい
so we'll look back
それで振り返ってみましょう
What are you using your phone for?
電話を何に使っていますか?
Let’s give a few examples of an application that everyone sees very often.
誰もがよく目にするアプリケーションの例をいくつか挙げてみましょう。
For example, if you say
たとえば、次のように言う場合
you need to check the map
地図を確認する必要があります
you will find out
あなたは分かるでしょう
If according to some of our past data
過去のデータによると
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
most people are on mobile
ほとんどの人はモバイルを使用しています
The blue part is the mobile phone
青い部分が携帯電話です
The orange part is the computer
オレンジ色の部分がパソコンです
Most people just look up the map
ほとんどの人は地図を調べるだけです
I actually checked it on my phone.
実際にスマホで確認してみました。
The weather is also on the phone
天気も電話でわかる
Listen to music on your phone
携帯電話で音楽を聴く
you and others are using some facebook
あなたや他の人は Facebook を使用しています
In fact, many people have also gone to the mobile phone
実際、多くの人が携帯電話にもアクセスしています
If you don't believe me, go home and see your children
信じられないなら家に帰って子供たちに会いなさい
where to go to facebook
フェイスブックのどこに行くか
so you will find
だからあなたは見つけます
Actually a lot of work
実は大変な仕事
what we used to do on the computer
私たちがコンピューターで何をしていたのか
Slowly all moved to the mobile phone
徐々にすべてが携帯電話に移行しました
because it's so convenient
とても便利なので
And it has so many functions
そしてとてもたくさんの機能が付いています
OK
OK
good
良い
of course
もちろん
from this point of view
この観点から
let's ask another question
別の質問をしましょう
OK
OK
I want to address these so-called
私はこれらのいわゆる
For mobile phone users
携帯電話をご利用の方へ
what jobs are you looking for
どのような仕事を探していますか
do it on top or look at it from another angle
上から見るか、別の角度から見るか
you will notice
あなたが気づくでしょう
I want to send some messages to someone
誰かにメッセージを送りたい
I'm 90% on my phone
90％は携帯電話を使っています
Just like you are using Line
LINEを使っているのと同じように
Or work with your Messenger etc.
またはメッセンジャーなどと連携してください。
ok photos
わかりました、写真
you are not the only ones
あなただけではありません
83% of people do the same thing as you
83%の人があなたと同じことをします
send email?
メールを送る？
Many people also do it on mobile phones
携帯電話でもやっている人が多い
There are many, many jobs that do this
こういう仕事をする仕事はたくさんあります
And of course there's a tablet, right?
もちろんタブレットもありますよね？
Of course, the tablet is also a big usage environment.
もちろんタブレットも大きな利用環境です。
Of course you can find out
もちろん調べればわかりますよ
a lot of searches
たくさんの検索
Some things will still be done on the tablet
一部の作業は引き続きタブレットで実行されます
Why because the screen is bigger
なぜか画面が大きいから
OK good
いいよ
But what?
でも何？
Everyone, the world will gradually change
皆さん、世界は少しずつ変わっていきます
OK, let's look at it from another angle
はい、別の角度から見てみましょう
how to use mobile phone how to use mobile phone
携帯電話の使い方 携帯電話の使い方
Guys, let's look at it from two angles
皆さん、2つの角度から見てみましょう
what if
仮に
You're using a browser on your phone to search for something
携帯電話のブラウザを使用して何かを検索している
Looking for information OK
情報探しOK
what kind of work is done on it
どのような作業が行われているのか
what did you watch
あなたは何を見たの
Of course you have something here
もちろん、ここには何かがあります
Like Google, Facebook, etc.
GoogleやFacebookなどのように。
This is done with Browseing
これはブラウジングで行われます
But I have to say on the phone
でも電話で言わなきゃいけない
because it has a small screen
画面が小さいので
In fact, what do most people use
実際、ほとんどの人は何を使っていますか
In fact, most people use RUN App
実際、ほとんどの人が RUN アプリを使用しています
These so-called applications
これらのいわゆるアプリケーションは、
What about the app?
アプリはどうですか？
In fact, like Facebook, Facebook, etc.
実際、Facebook、Facebook などのように。
are the most used
最もよく使われている
Okay, of course we're here
はい、もちろんここにいます
You should probably agree
あなたもおそらく同意するはずです
You do a lot on your phone
あなたは電話でたくさんのことをします
Then let's first define what is called App
次に、最初にアプリと呼ばれるものを定義しましょう
What is an application
アプリケーションとは何ですか
What about the application, the so-called App
アプリケーション プログラム、いわゆるアプリについてはどうでしょうか。
refers to the smartphone
スマートフォンのことを指します
on tablet
タブレットで
or even on some mobile devices
または一部のモバイルデバイスでも
some apps used
いくつかのアプリを使用
We call it App
私たちはそれをアプリと呼んでいます
OK
OK
Well, if you have an app, someone will sell your app
まあ、あなたがアプリを持っていれば、誰かがあなたのアプリを販売するでしょう
OK so all these apps
OK、これらのアプリはすべて
There are so-called App stores
いわゆるアプリストアがあります
Just like you can see in Apple
Appleで見られるのと同じように
Or even in Taiwan Mobile
あるいは台湾モバイルでも
They all have these apps
全員がこれらのアプリを持っています
OK
OK
well that
まあそれは
The so-called store of these apps
これらのアプリのいわゆるストア
It allows mobile device users
モバイルデバイスユーザーに許可します
Internet via Wi-Fi
Wi-Fiによるインターネット
An app connected to a mobile network
モバイルネットワークに接続されたアプリ
store for this app
このアプリのストア
Download your program for free or for a fee
プログラムを無料または有料でダウンロードする
Then it's easy to put on it
それなら貼りやすいですよ
Then these so-called App stores
それから、これらのいわゆるAppストア
In the beginning, of course, it was Apple
もちろん最初は Apple でした
A year later, Google came out with
1 年後、Google は
Of course there will be more and more
もちろんこれからも増えていきますが
First App Store
一開始App Store
when it was founded by apple
アップルが設立したとき
It's not just for the iPhone
iPhoneに限った話ではない
Your iPad Touch
あなたのiPad Touch
And these larger tablets for the iPad
そして、これらのiPad用のより大きなタブレット
so that everyone can publish
誰でも公開できるように
and be able to download these associated programs
これらの関連プログラムをダウンロードできること
Then of course anyone starts to feel that
そうすれば当然誰でもそう感じ始めます
Then I can also write my App
そうすれば、自分のアプリも書くことができます
I upload and I can also sell it to others
アップロードして他の人に販売することもできます
So it’s not just about downloading and using
つまり、ダウンロードして使用するだけではありません
It also makes selling easier
販売もしやすくなります
you can go up directly
直接登ることができます
anyone can put something
誰でも何かを置くことができます
It's easy to sell to someone in another corner of the world
世界の片隅にいる人に売るのは簡単だ
So many things changed accordingly
それに応じて非常に多くのことが変わりました
What app stores are there?
どのようなアプリストアがありますか?
For example, Apple's App Store
たとえば、Apple の App Store
And there's Google's called Play
そしてGoogleのPlayというものがあります
they all have a name
彼らは皆名前を持っています
Windows is called Phone Store
Windows は電話ストアと呼ばれます
The so-called black media machine
いわゆるブラックメディアマシン
Blackberry also has its
ブラックベリーには、
and Amazon's
そしてアマゾンの
and Samsung
とサムスン
Of course not only these things
もちろんこれらだけではありません
Let's say this is Windows
これが Windows だとしましょう
This is Apple's App Store
これはAppleのApp Storeです
Then everyone can upload it
そうすれば誰でもアップロードできるようになります
Of course if you want to upload
もちろんアップロードしたい場合は
Inside Apple he asked to say
Apple社内で彼はこう言いたいと頼んだ。
you have to pay the annual fee
年会費を支払わなければなりません
He usually pays about 99 dollars a year
彼は通常年間約99ドルを払っています
I can become his member
彼のメンバーになれるよ
if i want to upload something
何かをアップロードしたい場合
he has to check first
彼はまず確認しなければならない
then you can download
ダウンロードできます
If he sells you something for 100 bucks
もし彼があなたに何かを100ドルで売ってくれたら
He wants to draw 30 yuan
彼は30元を引き出したいと考えています
Of course the developer
もちろん開発者も
You can get 70 yuan
70元もらえるよ
ok of course
もちろんです
The 30 yuan he claimed was for maintenance and other expenses
彼が主張した30元はメンテナンスやその他の費用だった
Not only Apple
アップルだけじゃない
Of course, Google will also join the battle soon
もちろん、Googleもすぐに参戦するだろう
He is now called Google Play
現在は Google Play と呼ばれています
also the same
また同じです
But Google is a little different
しかしGoogleは少し違います
Where is it?
それはどこにある？
Google says I only charge you once
Googleはあなたに請求するのは1回だけだと言います
like 25 dollars
25ドルみたいな
It can be used for life from now on
これから一生使える
you don't have to pay me every year
毎年私に支払う必要はありません
But Google has another idea
しかしGoogleには別の考えがある
He said that anyone can upload and anyone can download
誰でもアップロードでき、誰でもダウンロードできると彼は言いました
But of course you imagine
しかし、もちろんあなたは想像します
if it is like this
このような場合
you have an app
アプリをお持ちですか
It is easier for you to upload
アップロードが簡単になります
Of course bad guys can upload
もちろん、悪意のある人がアップロードすることもできます
so what does it mean
それで、それはどういう意味ですか
Everyone throws things up
誰もが物事を吐きます
Then you can just pull the thing down and use it
その後、それを下に引き下げて使用するだけです
will you be poisoned
中毒になりますか
Wait, these problems may follow
待ってください、このような問題が発生する可能性があります
Of course it's the other way around
もちろんその逆です
if someone censored
誰かが検閲した場合
You say it's safer
そのほうが安全だと君は言う
But the problem is more troublesome
しかし問題はもっと厄介だ
You have waited for a long time and haven't put it on the shelves
長い間待ったのに棚に並べていない
even sometimes doubt
時には疑いさえする
Apple may have deliberately kept him out of the shelves
Appleは意図的に彼を棚から遠ざけた可能性がある
because he might be doing something like that
彼はそのようなことをしているかもしれないから
Of course these are all possible predictions
もちろん、これらはすべて可能な予測です
Not only that, he also does Windows
それだけでなく、Windows も実行します。
Just like you guys on your Windows tablet
Windows タブレットを使用している皆さんと同じように
Now even on your PC
今ではあなたのPCでも
You put Windows 8, Windows 10
Windows 8、Windows 10を入れます
You can download it in his App Store
彼のApp Storeからダウンロードできます
can download some of your software
ソフトウェアの一部をダウンロードできます
installed on your computer
あなたのコンピュータにインストールされている
And of course your phone
そしてもちろんあなたの携帯電話も
more than that
それ以上
Taiwan's telecom operators also want to count this business
台湾の通信事業者もこのビジネスに注目したいと考えている
So the telecom operator also provided him with the App Store
そのため、通信事業者は彼に App Store も提供しました
You can also download your stuff
自分の作品をダウンロードすることもできます
Like Chunghwa Telecom doing this Hami
中華電信がハミをやっているように
Of course, Yuanchuan also does this.
もちろん、ユアンチュアンもこれを行います。
you can imagine
想像できるでしょう
If this is the case, of course the Taiwan Revolutionary Committee will also do this.
そうなれば、台湾革命委員会も当然そうするだろう。
OK
OK
Do you only have telecom companies doing this?
こういうことをやっているのは通信会社だけですか？
of course not
もちろん違います
OK
OK
Of course what else is included?
もちろん他には何が入っているのでしょうか？
Including mobile phones like Samsung
サムスンなどの携帯電話を含む
he also wants to do this business
彼もこのビジネスをやりたいと思っています
Bigger wants to sell things
大きい人は物を売りたい
OK
OK
good
良い
Let's compare a little bit with these so-called App Store
これらのいわゆるApp Storeと少し比較してみましょう
you can see
見ることができます
Whether it is Apple or
アップルであろうと、
Windows is also good
ウィンドウズもいいですね
Google is also good
グーグルもいいですね
Or Chunghwa Telecom, Far EasTone, etc.
または中華電信、Far EasToneなど。
They both serve different operating systems
どちらも異なるオペレーティング システムに対応しています
like some like this one
このような人のように
This may be Taiwan's Big Brother
これは台湾のビッグブラザーかもしれない
He basically said that there are many service providers
基本的に、サービスプロバイダーはたくさんあると彼は言いました
Not just Windows
Windowsだけではありません
and including Apple's
Appleも含めて
Also includes Android
Androidも含まれます
they all have different ideas
彼らは皆異なる考えを持っています
to compete with each other in the market
市場で互いに競争する
But they all have a share
しかし、彼ら全員に分け前がある
because he could be a good source of profit
彼は良い収入源になる可能性があるから
There is an App Store
App Storeがあります
from above
上から
Many apps can be downloaded for use
多くのアプリをダウンロードして使用できます
of course like this
もちろんこのように
before i go on
先に進む前に
I'll go back and do a little more with you guys.
戻って皆さんともう少しやってみます。
Introduce the idea of ​​Android
Androidの考え方を紹介
and its environment
とその環境
Let's look at what's behind it
その背後にあるものを見てみましょう
Do you have any questions?
何か質問がありますか？
Welcome to ask questions or click me
ようこそ、質問するか、私をクリックしてください
Let's answer together later
後で一緒に答えましょう
Ok Android what is Android?
はい、アンドロイドアンドロイドとは何ですか?
Android is an open source
Android はオープンソースです
open source operating system
オープンソースのオペレーティングシステム
A Linux-based platform
Linuxベースのプラットフォーム
So its bottom layer is a Linux operating system
つまり、その最下層は Lenux オペレーティング システムです
It has some environment on it
何らかの環境が備わっています
so we call it a platform
だから私たちはそれをプラットフォームと呼びます
what to say now
今何を言うべきか
Google's entire ecosystem
Google のエコシステム全体
resulting action platform
結果として得られるアクションプラットフォーム
fastest growing in the world
世界で最も急速に成長している
It now holds about 82% of a market
現在、市場の約 82% を占めています
Of course it's not just the phone.
もちろん電話だけではありません。
you should notice
あなたは気づくべきです
including some TV platforms like
などのいくつかのテレビプラットフォームを含む
There are many starting to adopt Android
Android を導入し始めている企業がたくさんあります
ok that's natural
わかりました、それは自然なことです
Then everyone will say come down again
そしたらみんなまた降りて来いと言うだろう
It's not just your phone
それはあなたの電話だけではありません
not just your tv
あなたのテレビだけではありません
You should also notice that Apple and Google
Apple と Google にも注目してください。
want to sell stuff to put on your car
車に取り付けるものを売りたい
OK, of course it's not just like that
OK、もちろんそれだけではありません
After doing some business and thinking about wearing fashion later
用事が終わって、その後ファッションをしようと考えた後
Is there any way how to make a connection with him?
彼と関係を築く方法はありますか？
Okay, let's talk about this topic later.
さて、この話題については後で話しましょう。
Of course, this is just to give you a feeling.
もちろん、これは単に気分を伝えるためのものです。
Underneath is the core of a Linux operating system
その下には Linux オペレーティング システムのコアがあります
Above the whole thing Android
Android のすべてを超えて
They thought of this set of things to put on top of this core
彼らはコアの上に置くこのセットを考えました
different developers
さまざまな開発者
has its different roles to play
果たすべきさまざまな役割がある
For example, some developers in Taiwan
たとえば、台湾の一部の開発者は、
he does some hardware stuff
彼はハードウェア関連の仕事をしています
He can stuff relevant things into this Korean library
彼はこの韓国の図書館に関連するものを詰め込むことができる
It can be easily plugged into the whole system.
システム全体に簡単に接続できます。
Of course, this forms an entire ecosystem on top of it.
もちろん、これによりその上にエコシステム全体が形成されます。
well that
まあそれは
Let me first tell you what an operating system is
まずオペレーティングシステムとは何かを説明しましょう
The operating system is when you turn on the computer
オペレーティング システムは、コンピューターの電源を入れると
just kept running
ただ走り続けた
The program that ends after you shut down is called the operating system
シャットダウン後に終了するプログラムをオペレーティングシステムと呼びます
Just like the operating system on your personal computer is Windows
パソコンのオペレーティング システムが Windows であるのと同じように、
OK
OK
That's on your phone Android
それはあなたの携帯電話 Android 上にあります
is your platform
あなたのプラットフォームは何ですか
The whole platform runs on it
プラットフォーム全体がその上で実行されます
OK
OK
In other words
言い換えると
It is an environment between our users and the hardware
ユーザーとハードウェアの間の環境です
All hardware it controls
制御するすべてのハードウェア
Services that provide all our stuff
私たちのあらゆるものを提供するサービス
that's up there
それはそこにあります
you can directly manipulate it
直接操作できます
You can also run some apps on it
いくつかのアプリを実行することもできます
Let everyone see some different APPs
みんなにいくつかの異なるアプリを見てもらいましょう
OK
OK
Or those who see you running
それとも、何を実行しているのか見てみましょう
This Word Powerpoint and so on these software
このWord Powerpointなどのソフト
well these are
まあ、これらは
what about these things
これらのことはどうですか
application software
アプリケーションソフトウェア
it runs on top of the operating system
オペレーティング システム上で実行されます
The operating system directly controls your hardware
オペレーティング システムはハードウェアを直接制御します
What is the mainstream operating system now?
現在主流のオペレーティングシステムは何ですか?
what about the first one
最初のものはどうですか
Of course Unix and Linux series
もちろんUnix系やLinux系も
What about Linux?
Linux についてはどうですか?
I just reported to you
先ほどご報告させていただきました
The operating system running under Android
Android 上で動作するオペレーティング システム
OK
OK
then it's an open source
それならオープンソースだよ
Wait a minute and I'll report to you
ちょっと待ってください、報告します
What is Open Source
オープンソースとは
OK
OK
Then they belong to a similar series
その後、それらは同様のシリーズに属します
We say the series of Unix and Linux
Unix と Linux のシリーズといいます。
And Unix
そしてUnix
At Bell
アットベル
Developed at Bell Laboratories
ベル研究所で開発
Developed from 1971 to 73
1971 年から 73 年にかけて開発
Then began to produce some branches
それからいくつかの枝を作り始めました
in 1977
1977年に
There is another branch called Berkeley Distribution
バークレーディストリビューションと呼ばれる別のブランチがあります
A fork of Berkeley's version of this
これのバークレー版のフォーク
And these things are called open source
そして、これらのものはオープンソースと呼ばれます
First of all what is open source
そもそもオープンソースとは
Open source is the software
オープンソースはソフトウェアです
It's written down this program it must be open
このプログラムは書かれているので開いておく必要があります
able to spread freely
自由に広めることができる
Basically its spirit is like this
基本的にその精神はこんな感じ
Mocking Touch's Always is made by Apple companies
Mocking Touch の Always は Apple 社によって製造されています
This is another mainstream operating system
これも主流のオペレーティング システムです
Another one is that you are very common
もう一つは、あなたは非常に一般的であるということです
Windows commercial operating system on personal computers
パーソナル コンピュータの Windows 商用オペレーティング システム
Alright then let's move on to Lenax
さて、レナックスに移りましょう
Because it is the most important core under Android
Android で最も重要なコアであるため
Lenax was actually a student at the time
レナックスは実際には当時学生だった
He thinks these are used in class
彼はこれらが授業で使われていると考えています
The homework system used for teaching is really bad
教育に使用されている宿題システムは本当にひどいです
So he read a book and made one
それで彼は本を読んで本を作りました
From now on everyone will be fine
これからはみんな元気でね
I just started adding things in.
ちょうど何かを追加し始めたところです。
The first version was in 1991
最初のバージョンは 1991 年でした
Published on the Internet in September
9月にインターネット上で公開
Since then, everyone has continued to add things to it.
それ以来、みんながそれに何かを加え続けてきました。
more prosperous
より豊かな
we just knew
私たちはちょうど知っていました
Lenix it is at the bottom of the whole Android
LenixはAndroid全体の最下位にあります
It hosts the entirety of our Android operating system
Android オペレーティング システム全体をホストします。
Under the hood it's basically an open software operating system
内部では基本的にオープン ソフトウェア オペレーティング システムです
OK good
いいよ
Then I will introduce one more thing to you now.
それでは、もう一つご紹介させていただきます。
Called Open Handset Alliance
オープンハンドセットアライアンスと呼ばれる
OK a coalition of so-called open handsets
OK、いわゆるオープンハンドセットの連合
What is the Alliance for Open Handheld Devices?
オープン ハンドヘルド デバイス アライアンスとは何ですか?
In fact, this thing is launched by Google
実はこれ、Googleが開発したものなんです
Because why is Google launching this thing
だってなぜGoogleがこんなものを立ち上げたのか
Google it's very smart
Google、とても賢いですね
OK Google says I'm going to do this business now
OK Googleは今からこのビジネスをやると言いました
What should I do with Windows
Windowsではどうすればいいですか
Windows said how much I would sell you for an operating system
Windows は、オペレーティング システムをいくらで売るかと言ってきました
He said I don't need money OK
彼はお金はいらないって言った、わかった
But what money does he earn from you?
しかし、彼はあなたからどれだけのお金を稼いでいるのでしょうか？
he earns advertising money
彼は広告料を稼いでいる
OK
OK
Because once the operating system without money
なぜなら、かつてはオペレーティングシステムにお金がなかったからです。
Let's do it together
一緒にやりましょう
After making these phones?
これらの電話を作った後は？
Sowen
ソーウェン
All the traffic flows to my Google
すべてのトラフィックは私の Google に流れます
'Cause everyone's coming to me
みんなが私のところに来るから
I know what you want to do
あなたが何をしたいのかはわかっています
And you are on my network
そしてあなたは私のウェブサイトにいます
I'll show you the ad
広告をお見せします
I just pay advertisers
広告主に金を払っているだけだ
so therefore
だからだから
He told you no money
彼はお金がないと言いました
Because he takes money from others
他人からお金もらってるから
OK
OK
What about Windows?
Windows についてはどうですか?
he wants to sell you this thing
彼はあなたにこれを売りたいと思っています
I found out that your things don't cost money
あなたの物にはお金がかからないことが分かりました
So of course Window is in trouble
もちろん、Window は問題を抱えています
That
それか
Google wants to do this business
Googleはこのビジネスをやりたいと考えている
Of course he can't do it by himself.
もちろん彼一人でそれを行うことはできません。
So he told a bunch of people
それで彼はたくさんの人に言いました
Let's make a mobile phone together
一緒に携帯電話を作りましょう
make money together
一緒にお金を稼ぐ
So he formed this organization
そこで彼はこの組織を設立しました
A Consortium of Open Handsets
オープンハンドセットのコンソーシアム
He organized such an alliance
彼はそのような同盟を組織した
just say
言うだけ
Telecom provider Mobile phone provider
通信プロバイダー 携帯電話プロバイダー
do hardware
ハードウェアをやる
all together
みんなで一緒に
let's make a phone
電話を作りましょう
my operating system is free
私のオペレーティングシステムは無料です
OK let's do it together
よし、一緒にやってみよう
That quickly assembled dozens of companies
それによりすぐに数十の企業が集まりました
That sounds good, of course, right?
もちろんそれは良いことだと思いますよね？
But he wants to make money in the end
しかし彼は最終的にはお金を稼ぎたいのです
OK of course this so-called this
OK、もちろんこれはいわゆるこれです
This open hand holds this alliance
この開かれた手はこの同盟を握る
he has a great mission
彼には大きな使命がある
He said he hoped to make a better mobile phone
彼は、より良い携帯電話を作りたいと語った
to our users
ユーザーの皆様へ
And everything is open
そしてすべてがオープンです
OK
OK
And what if you have any vision
そして、何かビジョンがあるとしたらどうでしょうか
we'll make it happen
私たちがそれを実現します
just his basic idea
彼の基本的な考えだけ
OK, smart, right?
わかりました、賢いですね?
So, a lot of people started to struggle to come together and do it together.
それで、多くの人が団結して一緒にやろうと奮闘し始めました。
Telecom providers include telecom providers in various places at home and abroad
通信事業者には国内外各地の通信事業者が含まれます
OK, some of you have also seen OK
OK、OKを見た人もいるでしょう
Including this everyone see this T-Mobile in the US
これを含めて、米国では誰もがこの T-Mobile を目にします
Very European Vodafone
非常にヨーロッパ的なボーダフォン
Or on the mainland, China Mobile, etc.
あるいは大陸、チャイナモバイルなどでは。
Handset for mobile phones
携帯電話用ハンドセット
Like our Acer and other companies
Acer や他の企業と同様に
Or chip companies like ARM
あるいはARMのようなチップ企業
Or software companies like Google Ibe, etc.
あるいはGoogle Ibeのようなソフトウェア会社など。
Or do some commercial companies
あるいはいくつかの営利企業をやります
For example, the companies he consults with
たとえば、彼が相談している企業は、
Everyone tangled together to make a mobile phone together
みんなで絡まって携帯電話を作ろう
OK, that's of course very smart.
もちろん、それはとても賢いことです。
soon to be a fad
すぐに流行る
swept the market very quickly
非常に早く市場を席巻した
Because everyone in this ecosystem
なぜなら、このエコシステムの全員が
can have a share
シェアを持つことができる
OK so everyone come in and do it
OK、じゃあみんな来てやってみよう
So after everyone has done
それで、全員が終わった後、
Sure enough, a lot of traffic flows into Google
案の定、Google には大量のトラフィックが流入します
OK then they make a lot of money
OK、それで彼らはたくさんお金を稼いでいます
OK his basic story goes like this
OK、彼の基本的なストーリーは次のとおりです
OK, then I just mentioned
OK、それでは先ほども言いましたが、
Lenix is ​​also good
レニックスもいいですね
Android is also good
アンドロイドもいいですね
It's an open source concept
それはオープンソースの概念です
open that is
開いて、それは
I bring this thing, I can change it
これを持ってきます、変更できます
I should give it to someone else after I'm done
終わったら誰かにあげればいいのに
OK so the concept of open source
OK、オープンソースの概念
that I'm free to walk again
再び自由に歩けるようになることを
Besides, you write a program
それに、プログラムを書くのは、
You have to give me this code
このコードを教えてください
After I finish writing, I also want to give it to others
書き終わったら人にも贈りたい
OK, so what did you change at this time?
さて、この時点で変更した点はどうですか?
must also remain open
開いたままにしなければなりません
i want to be able to walk
歩けるようになりたいです
And I can't stipulate that he can only be exclusive to a certain
そして、彼が特定のことだけを独占できるとは断言できません
For example, a mobile phone or a tablet
たとえば、携帯電話やタブレットなど
then this thing must be complete
それならこれは完成しているはずだ
And I can't restrict you to do this program with other programs
そして、このプログラムを他のプログラムと一緒に実行することを制限することはできません
I can't take a walk because of that.
そのせいで散歩もできない。
Your stuff still needs to be able to walk
荷物はまだ歩ける必要がある
The various ways of walking must be handled with skill
さまざまな歩き方を巧みに扱う必要がある
This means that both electronic files and written files should be able to walk
これは、電子ファイルと書面ファイルの両方が移動できる必要があることを意味します。
So it's a free walk
なので自由散策です
Its concept is like this
そのコンセプトはこんな感じ
Open source code means that everyone can see it
オープンソースコードは誰でも見ることができることを意味します
does not mean free
無料という意味ではありません
If you don't understand, you can still ask me to collect money for you
理解できない場合でも、お金を集めるように依頼できます
because I offer you my knowledge
私の知識をあなたに提供するからです
So I think openness and free are two different things
だからオープンとフリーは別物だと思う
open just saying i can show you
開いて、見せてもいいって言ってください
you can also watch
あなたも見ることができます
You don't understand what's going on in your house
あなたは家の中で何が起こっているのか理解していません
Of course, after opening up, it will be a very important change.
もちろん、オープン後は非常に重要な変化になります。
Because once it's open source
オープンソースになったら
In fact, the industry is booming
実際、この業界は活況を呈している
This knowledge also flows quickly
この知識もすぐに流れます
Of course, it is also very good for Taiwan.
もちろん台湾にとっても良いことです
Because it used to be 20 years ago
20年前もあったから
The so-called operating system is a great technology
いわゆるオペレーティングシステムは素晴らしいテクノロジーです
Because everyone doesn't know how to write
みんな書き方知らないから
It's everywhere now, isn't it?
今ではどこにでもありますね。
everyone knows how to write
誰もが書き方を知っています
Everyone knows how to change
誰もが変わる方法を知っています
Of course not only operating systems have open source
もちろん、オープンソースがあるのはオペレーティング システムだけではありません
There's a lot more open source
オープンソースは他にもたくさんあります
Give me some examples
いくつか例を挙げてください
For example, as a window interface
たとえば、ウィンドウインターフェイスとして
or even you stay soft
あるいはあなたも柔らかいまま
Some people use FarFox which is a soft gas
ソフトガスであるFarFoxを使用している人もいます
or even some challenges with Microsoft Office
または Microsoft Office に関するいくつかの課題さえあります
The so-called OpenOffice
所謂的OpenOffice
or even the database's
あるいはデータベースの
data transfer software
データ転送ソフト
There are also so-called web servers
いわゆるWebサーバーもあります
All kinds of things are open
いろんなものがオープンになっている
There are many companies you also find that say
と言う企業もたくさんあります。
I don't do it my way anymore
もう自分のやり方ではやらない
If a lot of people open source
多くの人がオープンソースになれば
People keep adding new things
人々は新しいものを追加し続けます
I'll just take part in their calculations
私は彼らの計算に参加するだけです
if that thing does well
それがうまくいけば
I'll use his stuff and continue to enhance it
私は彼のものを使用し、それを強化し続けます
Anyway, if things are bad, someone will come in.
とにかく、状況が悪ければ誰かが入ってくるでしょう。
go ahead and fix it
先に進んで修正してください
certainly
そうです
That's what a lot of open source people are thinking about doing this
それが多くのオープンソース関係者がこれをやろうと考えていることです
ok that's open source
はい、それはオープンソースです
of course you just say
もちろんあなたはただ言うだけです
In addition to the so-called open source code I just told you
先ほどお話しした、いわゆるオープンソース コードに加えて、
Linux runs Android on it
Linuxはその上でAndroidを実行します
it's all open
すべてオープンです
then everyone can share
そうすれば誰もが共有できるようになります
then i can be my phone
それなら私が電話になってもいいよ
ok wait
わかりました、待ってください
Of course, here is a quick summary for you.
もちろん、ここでは簡単な要約を示します。
what phone do i have
私はどんな電話を持っていますか
I can develop App on it
その上でアプリを開発できます
Of course there are some development environments
もちろん開発環境もある
I'll probably mention it to you guys a little bit soon.
おそらく、近いうちに皆さんにも少しお話しすることになると思います。
Android and other development environments
Android およびその他の開発環境
Of course, it was done in java at the beginning
もちろん最初はJavaでやってました
java is a programming language
Javaはプログラミング言語です
Later, some people made use of other development environments to do
その後、他の開発環境を利用して次のことを行う人もいます。
Including C++, Python
C++、Pythonを含む
Different open environments to do
さまざまなオープン環境
There are many of these environments
こういった環境はたくさんあります
Like I just asked you to mention this one
ちょうどこれについて言及するように頼んだように
Also includes Android Studio
Android Studioも含まれています
You can develop App on it
その上でアプリを開発できます
Can be directly developed on Windows
Windows上で直接開発可能
then put it on and so on
それからそれを着るなど
Well these different development environments
さて、これらの異なる開発環境
that many things can be done very well
多くのことがうまくできるということ
It actually has a variety of graphical interfaces
実際にはさまざまなグラフィカルインターフェイスがあります
you are on top
あなたはトップです
when developing
開発するとき
It can be done in a relatively simple way
比較的簡単な方法で行うことができます
OK good
いいよ
of course
もちろん
what did you look like after you finished the program
プログラムを終えた後はどんな様子でしたか
Let me tell you a little bit
少しお話しさせてください
OK everyone knows
OK、誰もが知っています
What are the things you download from Apps
アプリからダウンロードするものは何ですか
It's good to feel a little bit
ちょっとした気分になるのもいいですね
Normally we who write programs
普段、プログラムを書く私たち
write my program in a programming language
プログラミング言語でプログラムを書く
That in Android such a
Androidではそのような
In an environment like Android
Androidのような環境では、
Everyone generally uses a language like Java
一般に誰もが Java のような言語を使用します
for program development
プログラム開発用
What about after I develop
開発した後はどうですか
Then a program
それからプログラム
We generally call it a compiler
一般的にはコンパイラと呼んでいます
compile it
それをコンパイルする
After compiling
コンパイル後
will become another
別のものになります
almost executable archive
ほぼ実行可能なアーカイブ
What about this file?
このファイルはどうですか
Java has a very special concept called
Java には、と呼ばれる非常に特別な概念があります。
This BuyCode
この購入コード
We call it BuyCode
私たちはそれをBuyCodeと呼んでいます
It appeared after it was compiled
コンパイル後に表示されました
The shape of this file
このファイルの形状
It looks like something class
何かのクラスのように見えます
OK
OK
what's so special about this program
このプログラムの何が特別なのか
I want to report to you
あなたに報告したいのですが
This program is especially
この番組は特に
where is it
それはどこにある
I used to be on a certain station
ある駅にいた
For example, the program I wrote on the X86 machine
たとえば、X86 マシンで書いたプログラム
This program cannot be directly moved to
このプログラムを直接移動することはできません
another company
他社
For example, Motorola
たとえば、モトローラ
The things done on the CPU run directly
CPU 上で実行される処理は直接実行されます
Can't directly move to
直接移動できません
Run directly on the CPU of the Arm company
Arm社のCPU上で直接動作
is not possible
それは不可能
Because the cross machine cannot run
クロスマシンは走れないので
But where is the greatness of Jiafa?
しかし、ジアファの偉大さはどこにあるのでしょうか？
it is cross platform
それはクロスプラットフォームです
Once I compile
コンパイルしたら
on this machine on that machine
このマシンで、あのマシンで
all can run
全員が走れる
Then why is there such a thing
ではなぜそんな事があるのか
It's actually the concept
実はそれがコンセプトなんです
on the real machine
実機で
ran a thing called a so-called virtual machine
いわゆる仮想マシンと呼ばれるものを実行しました
above is running your program
上でプログラムを実行しています
Then your program is actually running on a virtual machine
これで、プログラムは実際に仮想マシン上で実行されます。
And this virtual machine
そしてこの仮想マシンは
can be placed on any machine
どのマシンにも設置可能
Your program goes to the place of the virtual machine
プログラムが仮想マシンの場所に移動します
is safe
安全です
can be moved at will
自由に動かすことができる
So what if my program wants to run on another machine?
では、私のプログラムを別のマシンで実行したい場合はどうすればよいでしょうか?
As long as there is a virtual machine on that machine you can run
そのマシン上に仮想マシンが存在する限り、実行できます。
so what to do
じゃあ何をすればいいの
So it means that the app I wrote is my program
つまり、私が書いたアプリが私のプログラムであるということになります
Whether it's made by Samsung
サムスン製かどうか
No matter it is made by HTC, it can run
HTC製なら何でも動く
Because what I run out of is cross-platform
私に不足しているのはクロスプラットフォームだからです
I'm running on a virtual machine
仮想マシン上で実行しています
so you don't worry about saying
だから言っても心配しないでください
What about the program on my phone?
私の携帯電話のプログラムはどうですか?
It's Samsung's mobile phone with some apps running on it
これはサムスンの携帯電話で、いくつかのアプリが実行されています
Can I also download it on another machine
別のマシンにもダウンロードできますか
the answer is yes
答えははいです
Because of this so-called virtual machine concept
このいわゆる仮想マシンの概念のため、
So the code is no longer bound to a certain machine
したがって、コードは特定のマシンにバインドされなくなります
it can be tied
それは結ぶことができます
OK good
いいよ
It's interesting when the concept comes out
コンセプトが出てくると面白いですね
OK of course
もちろんOK
Before you run this program
このプログラムを実行する前に
Of course you have to convert it to the Android environment
もちろんAndroid環境に変換する必要があります
It also has a tool called DX
DXというツールもあります
will convert it to this
これに変換します
will do some optimization work
いくつかの最適化作業を行います
make it on your android
あなたのアンドロイドで作ってください
Running performance can be better
走行性能が向上する可能性がある
OK good
いいよ
So so far, it's
これまでのところ、それは
At your
あなたのところで
This is what the program running on your phone looks like
携帯電話で実行されているプログラムは次のようになります
What do you guys download from the App Store?
皆さんはApp Storeから何をダウンロードしますか？
You go to the App Store and if you make an app
App Store にアクセスしてアプリを作成すると、
If you want to put it on the App Store for people to download
人々がダウンロードできるように App Store に置きたい場合
Basically it does one more conversion
基本的にもう1回変換を行います
with another tool called AAPT
AAPT という別のツールを使用する
After you make a package
パッケージを作成した後
It's called the point APK program
それはポイントAPKプログラムと呼ばれます
So the program you downloaded in the App Store
つまり、App Storeでダウンロードしたプログラムは
Just click the APK program
APKプログラムをクリックするだけです
So after downloading, it will be decompressed
したがって、ダウンロード後は解凍されます
Just put it on and run
履いて走るだけ
That's the basic concept
それが基本的なコンセプトです
So in this slide, I mainly want to tell you two things
このスライドでは主に 2 つのことをお伝えしたいと思います
The first thing is on the phone
まずは電話で
The running app is cross-platform
実行中のアプリはクロスプラットフォームです
On this machine and that machine no matter what processor you are running
このマシンでもあのマシンでも、どのプロセッサを実行しているかは関係ありません
Whether it's Motorola's
モトローラ製かどうか
It doesn't matter which one of Apple's is the same, you can run
Apple のどれが同じかは問題ではありません。実行できます。
Because it is running on a virtual machine
仮想マシン上で実行されているため
There is also a virtual machine on top of the entity
エンティティの上には仮想マシンもあります
and only then run your program
そしてプログラムを実行するだけです
OK, so the virtual machine can be implemented on different machines
OK、仮想マシンは別のマシンに実装できます
Your layers can then be moved on top of
レイヤーをその上に移動できます。
OK of course other than that
もちろんそれ以外でもOK
I'm telling you
言ってるよ
In fact, in the end, after packaging this thing, it will be on your App Store.
実際、これをパッケージ化すると、最終的には App Store に掲載されることになります。
you can download
ダウンロードできます
Download it, unzip it, and install it
ダウンロードして解凍し、インストールします
OK, that layer runs on top
OK、そのレイヤーが一番上にあります
Let me tell you a few concepts
いくつかの概念をお話しします
What about the design of our mobile phone?
携帯電話のデザインはどうでしょうか？
It's a little bit different from your current desktop computer.
現在のデスクトップコンピュータとは少し異なります。
What about desktop computers?
デスクトップコンピュータはどうでしょうか？
if you can imagine
想像できれば
Can I run many levels
多くのレベルを実行できますか
It doesn't matter if your Office Powerpoint can be cut and cut
Office Powerpoint が切れても切れても問題ありません
But a phone isn't like your desktop computer after all.
しかし、結局のところ、電話はデスクトップコンピュータとは異なります。
It's just something you hold in your hand
それはただ手に持つものです
It doesn't have a big screen
大きな画面はありません
You seem to only do one thing at a time
あなたは一度に一つのことしかやらないように見える
OK of course you can listen to music
もちろん音楽を聴くこともできます
Then send a message to others
次に、他の人にメッセージを送信します
OK can also be OK
OKもOKです
But what about when you're looking at your phone?
しかし、携帯電話を見ているときはどうでしょうか？
Seems to be the foreground branch
手前の枝のようです
also because of this
これのせいでもあります
Its design concept is a little different
デザインコンセプトが少し違います
OK
OK
First of all, let me just say a few names.
まず、いくつか名前を挙げておきます。
OK, then I'll tell you a little bit about
OK、それでは少しお話します
what its concept looks like
そのコンセプトはどのようなものですか
on the phone
電話で
What about Android phones?
Android スマートフォンについてはどうですか?
We say a thing is called activity
物事を活動と呼ぶと言います
called Activity
アクティビティと呼ばれる
In fact it is used to display a screen
実際には画面を表示するために使用されます
OK it's doing one thing
OK、やっていることは一つです
it interacts with our users
ユーザーと対話します
Except for the one thing that interacts with you
あなたと関わるたった一つのことを除いて
In fact, there is something running behind
実は後ろで何かが動いている
OK, for example, helping you download something
OK、たとえば、何かのダウンロードを手伝ってください
The latter thing is generally called a service
後者は一般にサービスと呼ばれます
it executes in the background
バックグラウンドで実行されます
It may be downloading from the remote end
リモート側からダウンロードしている可能性があります
What about after that?
その後はどうですか？
Activity interacts with you
アクティビティはあなたと対話します
OK at the same time
同時にOK
You have a lot of things running together on this phone
この電話ではたくさんのことを一緒に実行できます
some material is shared
一部の情報は共有されています
OK, if it has to do this thing
OK、これを行う必要がある場合
It puts some data
いくつかのデータを入れます
do some integration
何らかの統合を行う
combined for use by other programs
他のプログラムで使用するために結合される
It is called Content Provider
コンテンツプロバイダーと呼ばれます
There's still a lot of work going on on the phone.
電話ではまだ多くの作業が行われています。
Including saying that your battery is not very good
バッテリーの調子が悪いということも含めて
The phone will notify you that the battery is low
携帯電話はバッテリーが低下していることを通知します
what are you going to do then
それで何をするつもりですか
so some notifications will appear
いくつかの通知が表示されます
Then if you write some programs on it
次に、それにいくつかのプログラムを書くと
can also receive some responses from these systems
これらのシステムからの応答も受信できます
And some of this requirement
そして、この要件の一部は
then you can do something
それなら何かできるよ
Well, if that's the case
まあ、そうだとしたら
Let's start to see how the mobile phone works
電話がどのように機能するかを見てみましょう
First you open something on your phone
まず携帯電話で何かを開きます
The idea on the phone is this
電話でのアイデアはこれです
there is something running activity
何かが実行中のアクティビティがあります
do some processing with you in front
あなたを前にして何らかの処理をする
Then you open another thing
それから別のものを開けます
The next thing it does is put the
次に行うことは、
like a stack
スタックのように
It puts this activity 2
このアクティビティ 2 を置きます
Just stuff it on top of Activity 1
アクティビティ 1 の上に詰め込むだけです
OK so you see activity 2
OK、アクティビティ 2 が表示されます
Activity 1 ran to the background below
アクティビティ 1 は以下のバックグラウンドまで実行されました
What if you're driving a
を運転している場合はどうなりますか
Activity 3 just run to the top
アクティビティ 3 頂上まで走るだけ
so one on top of the other
つまり、一方を他方の上に重ねて
The thing on top of it is the front neck thing
その上にあるのはフロントネックのものです
What's underneath is called the background
その下にあるものを背景といいます
OK, of course you can imagine
OK、もちろん想像できます
there's a front neck you face it
前に首があります、あなたはそれに直面します
bottom is behind
下が後ろです
OK this is the idea of ​​the phone
OK、これが電話のアイデアです
Because it has a small screen, do one thing at a time
画面が小さいので、一度に一つのことをしてください
What's on top is the foreground, what's left is the background
上にあるものは前景、残っているものは背景です
Then if you press a return key,
その後リターンキーを押すと、
when jumping the top thing off
一番上のものから飛び降りるとき
that thing it destroys you
それはあなたを破壊するものです
Then move the back to the foreground
次に、背面を前面に移動します
why destroy
なぜ破壊するのか
In fact, this is because when mobile phones are being made
実は、これは携帯電話が作られているときからです。
because of its memory etc. it's small
メモリなどの関係で小さいです
Resources are limited, so it saves what it can
資源は限られているので、できる限り節約します
If that thing thinks you don't look at it, it will kill you
あれが君が見てないと思ったら君を殺すだろう
But of course this is just a concept right now
しかしもちろん、これは現時点では単なる概念に過ぎません
does not mean that it will continue to do so in the future
今後もそうし続けるという意味ではありません
But it also represents an idea of ​​the phone
しかし、それは電話のアイデアも表しています
once you look at one more thing
もう一つ見てみたら
What is in front is separate from what is behind
前にあるものと後ろにあるものは別である
it is handled differently
それは別の扱いです
Speaking of this, I actually tell you
これについて言えば、実はあなたに言います
Some ways to operate the phone
電話機を操作するいくつかの方法
I gave you some simple explanations
簡単な説明をさせていただきましたが、
let's see then
それでは見てみましょう
From then till now
それから今まで
Android development
Android開発
Android basically
Android基本上
There are new revisions almost every year
ほぼ毎年新しい改訂が行われています
No matter how it is revised
どんなに改正されても
Everyone noticed one thing
誰もが一つのことに気づきました
Its name is just named after dim sum
その名前は点心にちなんで名付けられました
Like the old one called Cupcat
カップキャットと呼ばれる古いもののように
Until now called Marshmallow
今まではマシュマロと呼ばれていました
This is the October version
こちらは10月バージョンです
So after a while there is a version
それでしばらくするとバージョンができます
all dim sum
すべての点心
Anyway
ともかく
These versions are basically shared by mobile phones and tablets.
これらのバージョンは基本的に携帯電話とタブレットで共有されます。
Except for a version like 3.0 Honeycomb
3.0 Honeycomb のようなバージョンを除く
So this is its development
これがその発展形です
Everyone, the progress is actually quite fast.
皆さん、本当に進歩が早いですね。
In terms of market share
市場シェアの観点から見ると
Everyone, the bottom one is Marshmallow
みなさん、下はマシュマロです
Because it didn't take long, right?
だって、そんなに時間はかからなかったんですよね？
The more you go to the top, you will see different versions
上に行くほど、さまざまなバージョンが表示されます
Of course, this is a lot of words to give you a feeling.
もちろん、これは感情を伝えるための言葉がたくさんあります。
Aggel is the time axis
アゲルは時間軸です
This Y axis is 100% all android
この Y 軸は 100% すべて Android です
For example, at this point in time
たとえば、この時点では
This time point is from the perspective of October 2013
この時点は 2013 年 10 月の観点からのものです
You can see what version is used
使用されているバージョンを確認できます
what percentage
何パーセント
It's normal, and you see, as time goes by,
それは普通のことですが、時間が経つにつれて、
A new phone will come out with a new version
新しい携帯電話には新しいバージョンが登場します
The old ones are slowly passing by
古いものはゆっくりと通り過ぎていきます
When the new one first came out, the surplus rate was still very small.
新型が出た当初はまだ余剰率が非常に少なかった。
slowly grow up
ゆっくりと成長する
When I grow up, when time goes this way
大人になって、このまま時間が経つと
This bottom marshmallow
この下のマシュマロ
After a while it looks like this green
しばらくするとこんな緑色に見えます
And new ones come out, come out from under
そして新しいものが出てくる、下から出てくる
will keep going like this
このまま続くだろう
This is a state we see
これが私たちが見ている状態です
Here's a feel for some numbers for you guys
皆さんにいくつかの数字を感じてもらいましょう
so far
ここのところ
What is the market share of Android phones?
Android スマートフォンの市場シェアはどのくらいですか?
You can see that up to now, of course
もちろん今まで見てもわかりますが、
marshmallow is latest 6.0
マシュマロは最新の6.0です
it has 2.3%
2.3%あります
As you can see, many are still alive, right?
ご覧のとおり、多くの人がまだ生きていますよね？
Of course, the mobile phone does not mean that it will be broken after a year of use.
もちろん、携帯電話は1年も使えば壊れるというわけではありません。
many things are still alive
多くのものがまだ生きています
Look at the previous version 2.2
以前のバージョン 2.2 を見てください。
There is still 0.1% share
シェアはまだ0.1%
ok
Ok
anyway
ともかく
So everyone see Kickhand 4.3
だからみんなキックハンド4.3を見てください
What about version 4.4?
バージョン4.4はどうなるのでしょうか？
Actually still
実はまだ
Jelly Bean is still there too
ジェリービーンもまだあるよ
This is a very natural process
これは非常に自然なプロセスです
it will keep pushing
それは押し続けます
Occupancy rate will make some changes
稼働率は若干変動します
good
良い
then look again
それからもう一度見てください
What about different smartphones?
さまざまなスマートフォンについてはどうですか?
what is their occupancy rate like
入居率はどのくらいですか
everyone see
誰もが見る
Android phone on top
上部に Android スマートフォン
current market share
現在の市場シェア
About 82%
約82%
ok
Ok
So 8 out of 10 phones are Android phones
つまり、10 台中 8 台の携帯電話が Android スマートフォンです
besides that
それ以外に
Further down is iOS
さらに下には iOS があります
That is to say, when you see Apple's mobile phone
つまり、Apple の携帯電話を見ると、
what about share
シェアはどうですか
You probably see 14% now
おそらく現在 14% が表示されています
but it will float
でも浮いてしまう
In 2014
2014年に
See in 12 to 14 in 2015
2015 年 12 日から 14 日までにご覧ください
it keeps going up and down
それは上がったり下がったりを繰り返します
What about Windows phones?
Windows Phone についてはどうですか?
2.8 2.5 actually
実際は2.8 2.5
have been unable to rush up
急ぐことができなかった
About 2.3
約2.3
3% only
3%だけ
What about Blackberry?
ブラックベリーはどうでしょうか？
going from bad to worse
悪いほうへ悪化する
0.7、0.3
０。７、０。３
I don't know when it will disappear
いつ消えるか分からない
By 0.3 it has almost disappeared
0.3になるとほぼ消えます
Of course there are others
もちろん他にもあるよ
don't know what it is
それが何なのか分かりません
OK
OK
good
良い
This is from the perspective of mobile phone distribution
これは携帯電話の流通の観点から見たものです
then this is
それならこれは
In addition, it is the report of IDC
また、IDCのレポートです
The front is Garden's report
表面はGardenのレポートです
OK
OK
He also told you
彼もあなたに言いました
The distribution is about the same
分布もほぼ同じ
everyone see
誰もが見る
This is XO
XOです
Y axis is time
Y軸是時間
This is the Y axis is the market share
これは Y 軸が市場シェアです
What about the top one?
一番上のものはどうですか？
you can imagine
想像できるでしょう
This is the Android phone
これはアンドロイド携帯電話です
OK
OK
What about the blue one?
青いものはどうですか？
It is an IOS mobile phone
IOS携帯電話です
OK
OK
then further down
それからさらに下へ
everyone see
誰もが見る
This is other Windows
これは他のWindowsです
Bratberry, etc.
ブラットベリーなど
basically
基本上
The surveys conducted by the two companies are similar
両社が実施した調査は類似している
OK
OK
Both are about 82%
どちらも約82％
A market distribution of left and right
左右の市場分布
good
良い
What about the comparison of major phones?
主要な携帯電話の比較はどうですか？
take a quick look
ざっと見てみる
your IOS
あなたのiOS
The Phone Windows Phone Android Phone
電話 Windows Phone Android Phone
OK
OK
is their development environment etc.
開発環境などです。
market share
市場占有率
OK
OK
What about the development environment?
開発環境はどうなるのでしょうか？
from different development environments
さまざまな開発環境から
from java to different
Javaから別のものへ
OK
OK
Of course one is Android
もちろん1つはAndroidです
The bottom of Android is Linux
Androidの底辺はLinuxだ
Windows phones run Windows
Windows Phone は Windows を実行します
What about IOS?
IOSについてはどうですか？
It's actually an Apple phone
実はAppleの携帯電話なんです
It actually runs the Unix operating system at the bottom
実際には一番下で Unix オペレーティング システムを実行します。
OK
OK
Of course, there is Mark's operating system at the bottom
もちろん、一番下にはMarkのオペレーティングシステムがあります
It's running BSD Unix
BSD Unix を実行しています
OK
OK
Then stack it like this
あとはこんな感じで重ねていきます
But you can say it belongs to Unix
しかし、それは Unix に属すると言えます。
In this way, it is actually quite accurate.
このように、実際にはかなり正確です。
good
良い
Then you say
それからあなたは言います
Is it only young people who use mobile phones?
携帯電話を使うのは若者だけですか？
Actually not
実際にはそうではありません
OK
OK
Because just now many people said
だって今、いろんな人が言ってたので
Oops, we don't know how to use mobile phones anymore
ああ、私たちはもう携帯電話の使い方を知りません
OK
OK
are used by young people
若者が使っている
Actually not
実際にはそうではありません
OK
OK
Guys you belong to this group
あなたがこのグループに属している人たち
Of course there are many young people here
もちろん若者も多いですよ
OK
OK
Then take me as an example
じゃあ私を例に挙げてみましょう
look
見て
I belong to the 3 40%
私は 3 40% に属します
Everyone look at this over 65 years old
みんなこれを見ろ65歳以上
8% use mobile phones and smartphones
8%が携帯電話とスマートフォンを使用
20% aged 50 and over 55
20％が50歳以上55歳以上
If the tablet is nearly 30%
タブレットが30%近くの場合
This number may be a little more than you think.
この数字はあなたが思っているよりも少し多いかもしれません。
besides that look again
それ以外にもう一度見てください
What is the distribution of mobile phones?
携帯電話の普及状況はどうなっていますか？
Of course, at present, Android mobile phones have 57%
もちろん、現時点では Android 携帯電話が 57% を占めています。
iPhone, etc.
iPhoneなど
This has a different distribution
こちらは分布が異なります
This is a distribution of mobile phone and age
携帯電話番号と年齢の分布です
So we're not really special
だから私たちは特別ではない
In fact, each of us occupies a large proportion in it.
実際、私たち一人ひとりがその大きな部分を占めています。
What about the mobile phone?
携帯電話はどうですか？
Is it just that of course we just say
もちろんと言っているだけですか？
So many people use mobile phones
非常に多くの人が携帯電話を使用しています
what was the year like
今年はどんな年でしたか
Are we Taiwanese particularly aged?
私たち台湾人は特に高齢者なのでしょうか？
Actually not OK
実際には大丈夫ではありません
Someone is worse than us OK
誰かが私たちより悪いのはOK
let's take a look
見てみましょう
If you see the green part above, it is a TV
上に緑色の部分が見えればテレビです
So you said Indonesians like to watch TV
インドネシア人はテレビを見るのが好きだと言いましたね
Thai people see less
タイ人は物事をあまり見ていない
The blue part is your personal computer and your PC
青い部分はあなたのパソコンとあなたのPCです
The yellow part is the mobile phone
黄色い部分が携帯電話です
behind the tablet
タブレットの後ろに
everyone see
誰もが見る
If you look at it from this point of view
この観点から見てみると
you will see some very interesting fact
非常に興味深い事実がわかるでしょう
The distribution of people in different places is actually very different
場所によって人の分布は実際には大きく異なります
Of course, you are most concerned about what about us.
もちろん、あなたは私たちのことを最も心配しています。
take a look everyone
みんな見てください
Actually we are miserable
実際、私たちは悲惨です
This one still looks like a blue TV
これはまだ青いテレビのように見えます
red is your pc
赤はあなたのPCです
The green one is the phone
緑色のものは電話です
blue is
青は
sorry the purple one is your tablet
すみません、紫色のものがあなたのタブレットです
everyone see
誰もが見る
The use of so many screens above
上記の非常に多くの画面の使用
Our phone is the highest 197
私たちの携帯電話は最高の 197 です
actually amazing
本当に素晴らしい
So if you look at it this way
それでこうやって見ると
Actually we beat almost everyone
実際、私たちはほぼ全員を倒しました
right
右
Since the Japanese are not our opponents, right?
日本人は我々の相手ではないのでね？
Indonesians are nothing to look at, right?
インドネシア人は見るべきものではありませんよね？
Okay, so we look pretty good.
さて、見た目はかなり良いようです。
OK
OK
Taiwanese people are really sticky to their phones
台湾人は本当に携帯電話に執着する
OK good
いいよ
Then we are all glued to our phones, OK
そうなると、私たちは皆携帯電話に釘付けになります、OK
Actually we all know that OK
実際のところ、私たちは皆それを知っています。
Then why am I so clingy to my phone?
では、なぜ私はそんなに携帯にしがみついているのでしょうか？
because it can do many things
いろんなことができるから
So so let's take a look
それでは、見てみましょう
Why is this called a smartphone?
なぜこれをスマートフォンと呼ぶのか
So why is it called a smartphone?
では、なぜスマートフォンと呼ばれるのでしょうか？
Actually there's something behind it
実はその裏に何かがある
So that's why I use this phone
だから私はこの電話を使っています
Because you're not using it to make calls
通話に使用していないため
Use it to do many things OK
それを使っていろいろなことをしてOK
what things
どんな物
For example, the services behind you may include
たとえば、あなたの背後にあるサービスには次のようなものがあります。
Management of your personal information
お客様の個人情報の管理
For example, your blog
たとえば、あなたのブログ
your carrant
あなたのカラント
all your forms
すべてのフォーム
You are like me, everything is online OK
あなたも私と同じです、すべてがオンラインでOKです
when you often go outside
よく外に出るとき
you will check
あなたはチェックします
Is there any good food nearby? OK
近くにおいしい食べ物はありますか?
You will do some location based services
いくつかの位置情報ベースのサービスを実行します
location-based services
位置情報ベースのサービス
then you may do many other
そうすれば他にもたくさんのことをすることができます
For example, all my information is uploaded to the so-called
たとえば、私の情報はすべていわゆる
Go to Jobbox
ジョブボックスに移動
I can download it on every machine
すべてのマシンにダウンロードできます
OK
OK
so you have some
それで、あなたはいくつか持っています
some so-called general services
いわゆる一般的なサービス
Of course there are many others
もちろん他にもたくさんあります
Let's say you share a photo on
写真を共有するとします
or you read some news on it
またはそれに関するニュースを読んだ場合
so you'll notice
それで気づくでしょう
There's actually a lot of stuff you do on it
実際にやることはたくさんあります
like a blog
ブログのように
Many people read blogs
たくさんの人がブログを読んでいます
OK
OK
Many people spend a lot of time on it every day
多くの人が毎日それに多くの時間を費やしています
your form
あなたのフォーム
maybe you're not alone
たぶんあなたは一人ではない
You watch alone with many people
一人でたくさんの人と一緒に見る
For example, say your colleagues are doing something together
たとえば、同僚が一緒に何かをしているとします。
Everyone wants to know if you are busy now
あなたが今忙しいかどうか誰もが知りたがっています
He doesn't need to call you
彼はあなたに電話する必要はありません
He went directly to Google to see
彼は直接 Google にアクセスして調べました
you just share it
あなたはそれを共有するだけです
And of course you guys just looked at your map.
そしてもちろん、皆さんは地図を見ただけです。
OK
OK
you can find a lot of things on it
たくさんのものが見つかります
Your hard drive can be placed in the cloud
ハードドライブをクラウドに配置できる
everyone can go up and see
誰もが上がって見ることができます
You can go up and use it on every machine
すべてのマシンで使用できます
OK
OK
And you read the news
そしてあなたはニュースを読みました
or you can share
または共有することもできます
like your photo etc.
あなたの写真など
Then why do this thing
ではなぜこんなことをするのか
There must be something behind it to support these services
これらのサービスをサポートする何かが背後にあるはずです
Otherwise how can we get so many things
そうでなければどうやってこんなにたくさんのものを手に入れることができるでしょうか
you can imagine
想像できるでしょう
So many people put videos on their computers
非常に多くの人が自分のコンピュータにビデオを保存しています
Where did you put it?
どこに置きましたか
We all know that we have gone to the cloud
私たちは皆、クラウドに移行したことを知っています
There's a really huge machine over there in the back
奥にすごく大きな機械があります
it can hold almost unlimited amount of stuff
ほぼ無制限に物を収納できます
you want to check anything
何かを確認したいですか
When you hit Google to ingest something
何かを取り込むために Google を押すと
It's far away and I don't know where it is
遠くてどこにあるのか分かりません
After collecting the items for you, they will be delivered to you.
品物を集荷後、お届けいたします。
so what does it mean
それで、それはどういう意味ですか
Indicates that there should be a very huge machine behind it
その背後に非常に巨大なマシンがあるはずであることを示します
or a bunch of machines
あるいはたくさんの機械
in support of all your services
あらゆるサービスをサポートします
To provide the blog you just saw
先ほどご覧になったブログを提供するため
your facebook too
あなたのフェイスブックも
to do all these things
これらすべてのことをするために
So there must be a very powerful machine behind it
したがって、その背後には非常に強力なマシンがあるに違いありません
it provides you with all these services
これらすべてのサービスを提供します
OK
OK
Everyone knows that is more beautiful
その方が美しいことは誰もが知っています
people on facebook now
今フェイスブックにいる人たち
actually very very amazing
実際にはとてもとても素晴らしい
This is from 2012 to 2014
これは2012年から2014年までです
You see it keeps increasing every year
毎年増え続けているのがわかります
has been increasing
増加しています
That number is millions
その数は数百万です
Then you see
そうすればわかります
This 1393 million
この13億9,300万
what is that
それは何ですか
million trillion billion billion
百萬千萬億十億
OK there are 1.3 billion people
OK、13億人います
nearly 1.4 billion people
約14億人
Also use Facebook on the Internet
インターネット上の Facebook も利用する
OK so 1.4 billion people
OK、14億人
directly on top
直接上に
mean what
どういういみ
It must continue to be able to carry this matter
この問題を継続的に実行できなければなりません
And what?
そして何？
From 2012 until 2014
2012年から2014年まで
Until you find out all the way down
ずっと奥までわかるまで
it will continue to grow
それは成長し続けるだろう
Because the world's population is billions of people
世界の人口は何十億人もいるから
OK it will continue to grow
大丈夫、これからも成長していきます
What about the service behind it?
その背後にあるサービスについてはどうですか？
have to be able to keep supporting it
それをサポートし続けなければなりません
OK what does that mean
わかりました、それはどういう意味ですか
It must have a huge ecosystem behind it
その背後には巨大なエコシステムがあるに違いない
to push all this stuff
これらすべてを推進するために
OK
OK
so that our phone
これで私たちの電話が完成します
get all the services we want
必要なサービスをすべて受けられる
OK, so when you look at it from this angle
さて、この角度から見ると
then let's see
それでは見てみましょう
what are these things
これは何だ
what is
とは
Actually
実際
What about the things behind this huge service?
この巨大なサービスの背後にあるものは何でしょうか？
Cloud Computing
クラウドコンピューティング
ok you have a huge cloud platform over there
OK、そこには巨大なクラウドプラットフォームがあります
Because why is it called cloud
なぜクラウドと呼ばれるのか
you don't know where you are, do you?
自分がどこにいるのか分かりませんよね？
Is it right to face in the cloud anyway?
とにかく雲の中で直面するのが正しいのでしょうか？
I can't see it's there
そこにあるのが見えない
I can use what I want
使いたいものを使える
ok good
いいよ
So let's define what is cloud computing
それでは、クラウド コンピューティングとは何かを定義しましょう
What about cloud computing from an engineering perspective?
エンジニアリングの観点から見たクラウド コンピューティングはどうですか?
It basically provides a bunch of machines
基本的には多数のマシンを提供します
The machine is not necessarily physical
マシンは必ずしも物理的なものではありません
it is virtual
それは仮想です
Behind is thousands of machines on it
後ろには何千台ものマシンがあります
It supports all the services on it
すべてのサービスをサポートしています
ok, let’s run this thing on a real machine
よし、これを実機で実行してみよう
ok, the machines will continue to increase
はい、マシンは増え続けます
ok, let's look at it from an engineering point of view
さて、エンジニアリングの観点から見てみましょう
What about from a business point of view?
ビジネスの観点から見るとどうでしょうか？
basically it's a thing
基本的にそれは物だ
there's a way there's a service for me
私のためのサービスがある方法があります
it keeps growing
それは成長し続けます
ok
Ok
And it's always there
そしてそれはいつもそこにあります
It can support very large applications
非常に大規模なアプリケーションをサポートできる
Of course, what are the characteristics of cloud computing?
もちろん、クラウドコンピューティングの特徴は何ですか？
The first his platform is virtual
彼の最初のプラットフォームは仮想です
Where is it, you don't really care
それはどこですか、あなたはあまり気にしません
Maybe in Taiwan Maybe in Europe Maybe in America
たぶん台湾で たぶんヨーロッパで たぶんアメリカで
You don't mind too much, it's over there anyway.
あまり気にしないでください、とにかくそこにあります。
OK, what about the second one?
OK、2番目はどうでしょうか？
Everything has to be able to continue to grow
すべては成長し続けることができなければなりません
I want to be able to support a billion people now
今すぐ10億人をサポートできるようになりたい
In the future, this set of tools must be able to support two billion people
将来的には、このツール セットは 20 億人をサポートできる必要があります
Three billion people must continue to rise
30億人が立ち上がり続けなければならない
All his services must be efficient
彼のサービスはすべて効率的でなければなりません
unable to follow the process of growing up
成長の過程をたどることができない
when I click Google to do an ingest
インジェストを行うために Google をクリックしたとき
Come back in ten minutes, no
10分後に戻ってきてください、いいえ
OK press it and you will be back immediately
OK を押せばすぐに戻ります
OK for all service types
すべてのサービス タイプに OK
actually becomes very elastic
実際には非常に弾力性があります
when the clouds appear
雲が現れるとき
what is the impact on us
私たちにどんな影響があるのか
Of course the first
もちろん最初の
you'll find that says where do you put the pictures
写真をどこに置くかが表示されていることがわかります
Well, it's in my computer.
まあ、それは私のコンピューターの中にあります。
Of course there are problems
もちろん問題もあります
I also let it go OK
私も手放してOKです
it's nothing to be ashamed of
それは何も恥ずかしいことではありません
But where are many people
でも、人が多いのはどこですか
I don’t know where it’s right, in the cloud, right?
クラウドの中のどこが正しいのか分かりませんよね？
everyone can see
誰もが見ることができます
Your usage behavior is starting to change
あなたの利用行動が変わり始めています
Behavior Change
行動の変化
All manufacturers are also greatly affected
各メーカーも大きな影響を受ける
I can give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
Everyone see what is the most profitable for Microsoft
マイクロソフトが最も利益を上げているのは何か、誰もが知っています
What is Microsoft's most profitable
マイクロソフトの最も収益性の高いものは何ですか
It's not that Windows is the most profitable Office
Windows が最も収益性の高い Office というわけではありません
OK
OK
It's Word's Powerpoint that makes the most money with these things
これらで最も儲かるのは Word と Powerpoint です
But Microsoft is getting scared too
しかしマイクロソフトも怖くなってきている
Why
なぜ
because before
なぜなら前から
Before, you were using Word and Powerpoint
以前は Word や Powerpoint を使用していましたが、
Do you remember
覚えていますか
You're all done editing on this one machine and it's here
この 1 台のマシンでの編集はすべて完了し、ここにあります
What do you want to do when another machine is used
別のマシンを使用するときに何をしたいですか
copy him out
彼の真似をする
Get another machine and store it in
別のマシンを入手してそこに保管します
Everyone recently, everyone uses Office
各位最近 各位用 Office
did you find one thing
何かを見つけましたか
You can log in with an account
アカウントでログインできます
After you change it, it can exist on it
変更すると、その上に存在できるようになります
no idea where it is
どこにあるのかわからない
If you log in on another machine, you can watch it directly
別のマシンにログインすれば直接視聴できます
So it's clouded
だから曇ってるんだよ
things have gone up
物事は上がった
Why
なぜ
Because it actually faces the challenge of the cloud
実際にクラウドの課題に直面しているため
so therefore
だからだから
Include it app started changing
変更を開始したアプリを含める
It is no longer a stand-alone program
もはやスタンドアロン プログラムではありません
Start is a cross-machine program
スタートはクロスマシンプログラムです
Its service also does not allow you to modify the program on a machine
このサービスでは、マシン上のプログラムを変更することもできません。
Started going out across machines
マシンをまたいで外出し始めた
So this time you will find
そこで今回は、
office has entered its life and death challenge
オフィスは死活問題に突入した
Because includes OpenOffice
OpenOfficeが入っているので
Everyone including Google wants to do this business
Googleを含む誰もがこのビジネスをやりたいと考えています
It's so easy to make money, it has to make money
お金を稼ぐのはとても簡単なので、お金を稼がなければなりません
Once everything is online
すべてがオンラインになったら
After no longer the same machine
同じマシンではなくなった後
Your previous advantage may become your biggest obstacle now
これまでの利点が今では最大の障害になるかもしれません
everyone has to go up
誰もが上がらなければなりません
So the nature of apps starts to change
アプリの性質が変わり始める
Everything starts to go to the cloud
すべてがクラウドに移行し始める
ok
Ok
What about after going up?
上がった後はどうでしょうか？
How to use it on your mobile device
モバイルデバイスでの使用方法
It also begins to discover connections with the way you use it on your desk
また、デスク上での使い方との関連性も発見し始めます。
OK
OK
everyone pay attention
みんな注意してください
Recently, if you have used this Apple mobile phone
最近、この Apple 携帯電話を使用したことがある場合は、
you also noticed one thing
あなたも一つ気づいたことがある
your call to your cell phone
携帯電話への通話
Because your tablet can also call, right?
だってタブレットでも通話できるんですよね？
Why
なぜ
Because it actually starts to connect
実際に繋がり始めたので
start to link together
一緒にリンクし始める
This is an example to tell you
これはあなたに伝えるための例です
In fact your application
実際、あなたのアプリケーションは
No longer a stand-alone application
スタンドアロン アプリケーションではなくなりました
Start the network cloud thing
ネットワーククラウドを始める
start walking in that direction
その方向に歩き始める
The concept of desktop software
デスクトップソフトウェアの概念
Further down the time has begun to cease to exist
さらに時間が経てば存在しなくなり始めます
What started out as a decentralized web
分散型ウェブとして始まったもの
OK
OK
that's why
それが理由です
In fact, Microsoft now
実際、マイクロソフトは現在、
So hard to make a push to the cloud part
クラウド部分にプッシュするのは非常に難しい
because
なぜなら
the world has begun to change
世界は変わり始めた
It's not what it used to be
以前とは違います
of course
もちろん
It also provides us with great opportunities
それは私たちに素晴らしいチャンスも与えてくれます
OK
OK
It's like I'm telling you
まるであなたに言ってるようだ
What about cloud computing?
クラウドコンピューティングについてはどうでしょうか?
it has to be successful
それは成功しなければなりません
Of course there are several prerequisites
もちろん、いくつかの前提条件があります
Guys, what about after you put your photos in the cloud?
皆さん、写真をクラウドに置いた後はどうでしょうか?
you have to show others
他の人に見せなければなりません
you say sorry
あなたはごめんなさいと言う
I can't see it OK
見えないけど大丈夫
I don't know why OK
なぜOKなのか分かりません
you are very very depressed
あなたはとてもとても落ち込んでいます
because one thing is put in one place
一つの物が一つの場所に置かれているから
you should always have it
あなたはいつもそれを持っているべきです
availability is very important
availability非常重要
Anytime I can use it I can see OK
いつ使ってもOKです
not only that
それだけでなく
After I put things in the cloud
クラウドに物を置いた後
I'm worried about being stolen, right?
盗まれるのが心配ですよね？
i have some pictures
写真がいくつかあります
I have some information that was blocked by my test paper
テスト用紙によってブロックされた情報がいくつかあります
I am already very happy when I go to the cloud student
クラウド生に行くともうとても幸せです
if he can download
彼がダウンロードできれば
He has an exam tomorrow, right?
彼は明日試験ですよね？
so no
いいえ
I must lock it up OK
鍵をかけなきゃOK
My storage space will continue to grow OK
ストレージ容量は今後も増加し続けます。
can handle a billion people today
今日では10億人を扱うことができます
Can handle two billion people in the future
将来的には20億人を処理できる
Facebook will say
フェイスブックはこう言うだろう
Sorry, I only serve you 1.3 billion people today
申し訳ありませんが、今日私がサービスを提供できるのは 13 億人だけです
Sorry for the new person, I won't accept it OK
新規の方は申し訳ありませんが受け付けません。
no way right
まさか
He said try his best, try his best
彼は頑張って、頑張ってって言った
I can do two billion, three billion, I'm fine, right?
20億でも30億でも大丈夫ですよ？
so he doesn't move
だから彼は動かない
Countable growth
数えられるほどの成長
OK
OK
rapid growth
急成長
Not only you are storing and computing
保存したり計算したりするだけではありません
all things grow
全部のものは光ってる
Then what
じゃあ何
After everything is online
すべてがオンラインになった後
you guys noticed one thing
皆さんは一つのことに気づきました
If you are in the company
会社にいるなら
or you are in school
あるいは学校に通っています
did you notice one thing
一つ気づいたことがありますか
Many things are no longer available
もう手に入らないものもたくさんあります
OK
OK
for example
例えば
in my lab
私の研究室で
I've stopped buying some servers
一部のサーバーの購入をやめました
I rented it
レンタルしました
OK
OK
all online
すべてオンライン
machine broken
機械が壊れた
I hold him accountable
私は彼に責任を負わせます
OK
OK
Everything is on the Internet
すべてはインターネット上にあります
so my students
だから私の生徒たち
or assistant
またはアシスタント
To download any file
任意のファイルをダウンロードするには
I said go there and download it
そこに行ってダウンロードしてくださいと言いました
24 hours shop
24時間営業のお店
OK
OK
guaranteed to get
確実に手に入る
die and find him responsible
死んで彼の責任を見つけてください
right
右
Look everyone
みんな見てください
He has a license with me
彼は私と一緒に免許を持っています
he rented me this thing
彼は私にこれを貸してくれました
He guarantees me 24 hours
彼は私に24時間保証してくれる
365 days a day
365日
Every second must be able to walk
毎秒歩くことができなければなりません
and fast
そして速い
or he pays me
そうしないと彼が私にお金を払ってくれる
OK
OK
So actually notice that something is starting to change
それで実際に何かが変わり始めていることに気づいてください
Some hardware items are not available for purchase
一部のハードウェアアイテムは購入できません
I use pig software, can I still buy it?
pig ソフトウェアを使用していますが、購入できますか?
Of course you don't buy some software
もちろんソフトウェアを購入する必要はありません
Because there are no more machines, right?
もう機械がないからですよね？
I may just use that machine to type directly on it
そのマシンを使って直接何かを入力するかもしれません
It's fine to pay as long as it takes to sleep.
寝るのにかかる分だけお金を払って大丈夫です。
So things will change, right?
それで状況は変わりますよね？
So the new economic order of all things has gradually arrived
したがって、あらゆるものの新しい経済秩序が徐々に到来しています
Because many things I no longer need to acquire
もう手に入れる必要のないものがたくさんあるから
some things i bring with pigs
豚と一緒に持っていくもの
I'm a pig machine, I'm a pig software
私は豚のマシン、私は豚のソフトウェアです
I don't want it
欲しくない
I opened a shop, why do I buy so many machines
お店をオープンしたのに、なぜそんなにたくさんの機械を買うのですか？
I just talk to anyone, whether it's Amazon
Amazonであろうと誰とでも話すだけです
Whether it is Chunghwa Telecom, rent this computer room
中華電信かどうか、このコンピュータ室を借りてください
Just go straight up and open the shop
まっすぐ行ってお店を開けてください
If you want to expand today, just rent a few more machines
今すぐ拡張したい場合は、さらに数台のマシンをレンタルするだけです
got bigger
大きくなった
So you can grow up and get smaller at any time
だからいつでも大きくなったり小さくなったりできる
also sell us
私たちも売ってください
So a lot of things started to change
それで、多くのことが変わり始めました
I buy a software, I don't have to think about it for a long time
ソフトウェアを購入すれば、長い間それについて考える必要はありません
I rent it for two days and use it. I don’t like returning it to him.
2日間レンタルして使っていますが、彼に返すのは好きではありません。
Of course, many things have changed by then.
もちろん、それまでに多くのことが変わりました。
In fact, the cloud drives a lot of services behind it.
実際、クラウドはその背後で多くのサービスを推進しています。
Cause our mobile phone has a lot of power
だって私たちの携帯電話にはたくさんの電力があるから
Support turning into a smart phone
スマートフォン化をサポート
But it is actually changing our whole world
しかし、それは実際に私たちの世界全体を変えつつあります
not just like that
それだけではありません
let's go on
続けましょう
What is cloud computing
クラウドコンピューティングとは
When it comes to this, everyone will say
こうなると誰もが言うだろう
Cloud computing is in the very deep cloud
クラウド コンピューティングは非常に深いクラウド内にあります
something is running
何かが走っています
I can save things, I can run data
保存もできるし、データも実行できる
I just ask for what I want
欲しいものをただ聞くだけです
it does look like this
それはこのように見えます
Since there is a cloud, my things can exist on it
雲があるから私の物はその上に存在できる
Tell me, where is this cloud?
教えてください、この雲はどこですか？
it may not matter to you
あなたにとっては関係ないかもしれません
but some people care
でも気にする人もいる
For example, they care about hospitals and the government.
たとえば、彼らは病院や政府に関心を持っています。
He said
彼は言った
There is a cloud today and I put things on it
今日は雲があるのでその上に物を置きました
Many of my important health insurance information, if I put them there
重要な健康保険情報の多くをそこに置いておくと、
Today, the United States treats it as a leak.
現在、米国はこれを漏洩として扱っている。
OK, it doesn't seem to work, right?
OK、うまくいかないようですね？
or individuals, everyone's personally identifiable information has been downloaded
または個人、全員の個人を特定できる情報がダウンロードされています
no way, right?
まさかね？
So at this time, a lot of ideas came out, including what
このとき、いろいろなアイデアが出てきました。
What about clouds? Some are public clouds.
クラウドについてはどうでしょうか? パブリック クラウドもあります。
some are proprietary some are hybrid
いくつかは独自のもので、いくつかはハイブリッドです
The government may say that I want to build a cloud
政府はクラウドを構築したいと言うかもしれません
This cloud is used by all government units and is private
このクラウドはすべての政府機関によって使用されており、プライベートです
Then this Chinese Academy may also have a cloud
そうなると、この中国アカデミーにも雲がかかるかもしれない
OK then we have some things that might be more rentable
OK、それならもっとレンタルできるものがあるよ
We probably only use Google and the public cloud
おそらく Google とパブリック クラウドのみを使用します
You can do a lot of things on it
いろいろなことができます
After cloud computing, as I just mentioned
クラウドコンピューティングの後は、先ほど述べたように
It supports a huge application that provides the use of our mobile phones
携帯電話の使用を提供する巨大なアプリケーションをサポートしています
But at the same time, let's look at it again, since there is a cloud
でも同時に、雲があるのでもう一度見てみましょう
There are a few well-known nouns, let me explain to you a little
よく知られた名詞がいくつかありますので、少し説明させてください。
OK like what?
OK、どうですか？
Some of you have heard of cloud computing, you may have heard of the so-called
クラウド コンピューティングについて聞いたことがある人もいるでしょう。いわゆる
So software-level services, the so-called SARS
ソフトウェアレベルのサービス、いわゆるSARS
Platform-level services and so-called
プラットフォームレベルのサービスといわゆる
This infrastructure may be an architecture-level service
このインフラストラクチャはアーキテクチャ レベルのサービスである可能性があります
So what is software-level service?
では、ソフトウェアレベルのサービスとは何でしょうか?
Running this software is basically a service
このソフトウェアの実行は基本的にサービスです
like you use Gmail
Gmail を使用しているのと同じように
that is a software
それはソフトウェアです
where is this software running
このソフトウェアはどこで実行されていますか
You don't really care, do you?
あまり気にしないですよね？
Any machine can run
どのマシンも実行可能
Anyway, as long as you connect it, you can use it.
とにかく接続さえすれば使えるようになります。
Well, platform-level services
さて、プラットフォームレベルのサービス
like these things
こういったもののように
Just like the business Microsoft does
Microsoft が行っているビジネスと同じように
it runs a platform on it
その上でプラットフォームを実行します
Everyone has heard of Azoo
誰もが Azoo について聞いたことがあるでしょう
There are many development tools on it
多くの開発ツールが含まれています
So you don't have to rent a platform
したがって、プラットフォームをレンタルする必要はありません
There is no need to buy a database from him
彼からデータベースを購入する必要はありません
you just rent that thing for it
それをレンタルするだけです
You can develop things on it
その上で開発を行うことができます
you can do business
あなたはビジネスをすることができます
Or like Amazon does this business
あるいはAmazonがこのビジネスを行っているように
it provides these machines
これらのマシンを提供します
you can rent some machines for it
いくつかのマシンをレンタルできます
you can put things on it
その上に物を置くことができます
Let me give you another example
別の例を挙げましょう
How many of you have heard of box grabbing?
ボックスグラブについて聞いたことがある人は何人いますか?
What is Jobbox? Everyone, is it a piece of software?
Jobboxって何ですか? 皆さん、これってソフトウェアですか?
After I installed this software
このソフトウェアをインストールした後
I can move between several computers
複数のコンピュータ間を移動できる
share some files, right?
いくつかのファイルを共有しますよね？
After all installed, it will automatically
すべてインストールすると、自動的に
Change it here and help me sync
ここで変更して同期を手伝ってください
Change it here and copy it for me
ここを変更してコピーしてください
It helps me keep both sides the same
両側を同じに保つのに役立ちます
Then I tell Jobbox
それからジョブボックスに伝えます
I will buy 100GB from you a year
あなたから年間 100GB を購入します
OK 100 GIGA such a space
OK 100ギガこんなスペース
Does Amazon actually have its own machines?
Amazon は実際に独自のマシンを持っていますか?
Sorry, does Jobbox have machines?
申し訳ありませんが、Jobbox にはマシンがありますか?
Jobbox without machine
マシンのないジョブボックス
Jobbox is rented from Amazon
Jobbox は Amazon からレンタルされています
OK Amazon offers a lot of machines
OK Amazon はたくさんの機械を提供しています
what about these machines
これらの機械はどうですか
How much CPU and how much storage space?
CPUとストレージ容量はどれくらいですか?
Just rent from Jobbox
Jobbox からレンタルするだけ
Then Jobbox will be the second landlord
そうすれば、Jobbox が 2 番目の家主になります
Jobbox provides software services
Jobboxはソフトウェアサービスを提供します
Then I rent with Jobbox
それからJobboxでレンタルします
I want to buy 100GB OK with it
100GBを購入したいのですが、それでOKです
then i pay for it
それなら私が支払います
What about after Jobbox collects a lot of money?
Jobbox が多額の資金を集めた後はどうなるでしょうか?
Rent things from Amazon for cheaper
Amazonで物を安くレンタルする
So Jobbox
だからジョブボックス
second landlord
二番目の家主
He is software service
彼はソフトウェアサービスです
Amazon provides the machine
Amazon提供機器
he is the real landlord
彼が本当の家主です
So everyone makes their own money layer by layer
つまり、誰もが自分でお金を階層ごとに稼いでいるのです
This is from the point of view of cloud computing
これはクラウドコンピューティングの観点から見たものです
Cloud computing is actually a huge ecosystem
クラウド コンピューティングは実際には巨大なエコシステムです
can think about it
それについて考えることができます
Some people rent machines and sell machines
機械をレンタルしたり販売したりする人もいます
Just like we have a lot of people selling machines in Taiwan
台湾で機械を販売している人がたくさんいるのと同じように
Give these Google stores these companies
これらの Google ストアにこれらの企業を紹介します
Someone is manipulating the environment
誰かが環境を操作している
Companies like Google and Amazon
GoogleやAmazonのような企業
Let's continue to stack things on top of each other.
これからも何かを積み重ねていきましょう。
So at the bottom there is provided
したがって、一番下に提供されます
The whole cloud structure thing
雲の構造全体のこと
Someone provides the platform, someone provides the software
誰かがプラットフォームを提供し、誰かがソフトウェアを提供する
Someone provided the so-called solution
誰かがいわゆる解決策を提供した
he tells people what to do
彼は人々に何をすべきかを教える
How to build a system
システムの構築方法
So it's actually a huge ecosystem inside.
つまり、内部は実際には巨大なエコシステムなのです。
supports the entire so-called cloud computing
いわゆるクラウドコンピューティング全体をサポートします
What do you think is the difference between cloud computing and data storage in the past?
クラウド コンピューティングとこれまでのデータ ストレージの違いは何だと思いますか?
very different
とても違う
So you used to have a data center in this place
以前はこの場所にデータセンターがあったのですね
Then I have information, I'm afraid I won't see it
それなら情報はあるけど、見れないのではないかと思う
So I use another MIRROR over there
だから私はそこにある別のMIRRORを使用します
which side copy
どちら側のコピーか
copy to copy to
コピー先のコピー先
For fear of data loss
データ損失の恐れがあるため
Think about it, everyone in the cloud
クラウドにいる皆さん、考えてみてください
Is a huge data center that can grow
成長可能な巨大なデータセンターです
it will keep growing by itself
それは勝手に成長し続けるだろう
and it does all the backups by itself
すべてのバックアップを単独で実行します
do all the management
管理をすべて行う
You don't have to worry about these things anymore
もうこれらのことを心配する必要はありません
ok of course
もちろんです
In fact, how to use these services in this cloud
実際、このクラウドでこれらのサービスを使用する方法は次のとおりです。
Everyone is using it, right?
みんな使ってますよね？
like you use your phone
電話を使うのと同じように
your smartphone
あなたのスマートフォン
It's good to run all your blogs on it
すべてのブログをそれで実行するのは良いことです
run your facebook
フェイスブックを運営する
In fact, they are using the service behind
実際、彼らは背後でサービスを使用しています
so what is facebook
それで、フェイスブックとは何ですか
Facebook is the Service
Facebook はサービスです
Suffer as a Service
サービスとしての苦しみ
software as a service
サービスとしてのソフトウェア
So Facebook is like Gmail
つまり Facebook は Gmail のようなものです
it offers you a service
それはあなたにサービスを提供します
through this thing
このことを通して
You can get a lot of information
たくさんの情報を得ることができます
can do with everyone
みんなと一緒にできる
an interaction in this community
このコミュニティでの交流
Of course, there are many other things besides mobile phones.
もちろん、携帯電話以外にもさまざまなものがあります。
Including everyone who sees your personal computer
あなたのパソコンを見ている人全員を含む
or even on the tv
あるいはテレビでも
Now it is becoming more and more popular
今ではますます人気が高まっています
OK you can do an access to cloud data
OK、クラウド データにアクセスできます
OK, of course the platform has many possibilities
もちろん、プラットフォームには多くの可能性があります
You may be Windows, you may be Android
あなたは Windows かもしれないし、Android かもしれない
Of course you could be Apple
もちろん、あなたは Apple になることもできます
OK, well, there are actually many things behind it.
そうですね、実はその裏にはたくさんのことがあるんです。
just like you mentioned
あなたが言ったように
We have a huge machine behind the cloud
クラウドの背後に巨大なマシンがあります
run a lot of software on it
その上で多くのソフトウェアを実行する
They are available from my phone
私の携帯電話から利用できます
OK good
いいよ
What about during this use?
この使用中はどうでしょうか？
you probably do a lot of different things
あなたはおそらくたくさんの異なることをしているでしょう
Let's say you're doing a search for something
何かを検索しているとします。
For example, if you Google, who is Guo Dawei?
たとえば、Google で検索すると、Guo Dawei とは誰ですか?
ok ok of course
わかりました、もちろん
when you often ask some questions
よく質問するとき
you will find that say
そう言うのが見つかるでしょう
Your stuff seems to be getting smarter
あなたのものはますます賢くなっているようです
OK even
大丈夫です
you guys noticed something
君たちは何かに気づいた
Many of you use Gmail
Gmailを使っている方も多いのではないでしょうか？
Then if you go to buy a plane ticket
それで航空券を買いに行くと
when your
あなたのとき
When the confirmation letter of this ticket is sent to you sometimes
このチケットの確認メールが時々送られてくるとき
you will find one thing
あなたは一つのことを見つけるでしょう
when you look at your this one day
ある日あなたのこれを見ると
when you form d
あなたがdを形成するとき
You will find that it automatically added for you
自動的に追加されたことがわかります
ok then you will be scared
わかった、それでは怖くなるだろう
Why did you add something, right?
なぜ何かを追加したのですか？
mean what
どういういみ
For example, someone is peeking at your email, right?
たとえば、誰かがあなたのメールをのぞき見していますよね？
That is to say, when this thing is being transmitted
つまり、このことが伝わっているとき、
Some of this system and software are already learning
このシステムとソフトウェアの一部はすでに学習中です
Include it less than your email when sending
送信時にメールアドレスよりも小さい値を含めてください
Or when stored on its gmail platform
または、Gmail プラットフォームに保存されている場合
it's actually less
実際にはもっと少ないです
it knows something
それは何かを知っています
it knows a lot about you
それはあなたのことをよく知っています
then of course you should be afraid
それならもちろん怖がるべきだ
computer seems smart
コンピュータは賢いようです
it knows many things about me
それは私について多くのことを知っています
How does it know so many things about me?
どうやって私についてそんなに多くのことを知っているのでしょうか？
There must be a great artificial intelligence behind it
その背後には優れた人工知能があるに違いありません
So it will learn the above material
したがって、上記の内容を学習します
it will draw some conclusions
それはいくつかの結論を導き出すでしょう
Provide you with the so-called best service
いわゆる最高のサービスを提供する
But it also knows you best
しかし、それはあなたのことを一番よく知っているということでもあります
sounds scary
かなり怖そうです
The computer starts to learn from a large amount of data
コンピューターは大量のデータから学習を開始します
these things
これらの事
so he can make some judgments
そうすれば彼はある程度の判断ができるようになる
He offers you what he thinks is the best service
彼はあなたに最高のサービスだと思うものを提供します
Of course he makes the most money from you
もちろん、彼はあなたから最も多くのお金を稼いでいます
what is machine learning
機械学習とは何ですか
What about machine learning?
機械学習についてはどうですか?
basically a science
基本的に科学
He learns from a large amount of information
彼は大量の情報から学びます
Let's say you lose some rules to him
あなたが彼に対していくつかのルールを失ったとします。
he can judge
彼は判断できる
because you're dizzy
めまいがするから
so you can't speak
だからあなたは話すことができません
He said you might have had a stroke or you might have a cold
彼はあなたが脳卒中を起こしたか、あるいは風邪をひいたかもしれないと言った
or many ways of learning
またはさまざまな学習方法
Not just the learning of the so-called rules
いわゆるルールを学ぶだけではなく、
even so-called directed learning
いわゆる指示された学習であっても
you give him some strength
あなたは彼に力を与えます
He just makes some distinctions
彼はいくつかの区別をしているだけです
and then do some classification
それからいくつかの分類を行います
Then he starts to study
それから彼は勉強を始めます
know something
何かを知っています
Or give him information and he will start to distinguish
あるいは情報を与えれば彼は区別し始めるだろう
Or say you give him some cases
あるいは、あなたが彼にいくつかのケースを与えたとします
he learned
彼が学びました
so there are different techniques
だからさまざまなテクニックがあります
doing so-called machine learning
いわゆる機械学習を行う
From this information he can gain new knowledge
この情報から新しい知識を得ることができます
so he can make some judgments
そうすれば彼はある程度の判断ができるようになる
He also knows what to look for
彼は何を探すべきかも知っています
Well, of course, in this day and age
まあ、もちろんこのご時世ですので、
In fact, because of the entire cloud technology
実際、クラウド テクノロジー全体のおかげで、
Also due to the generation of large amounts of data
また、大量のデータが生成されるため、
We use above
上記で使用します
So another huge opportunity arose
そこでまた大きなチャンスが訪れました
It's not just cloud computing that's a huge opportunity
大きなチャンスがあるのはクラウド コンピューティングだけではありません
OK phone?
電話はどうですか？
Cloud computing is a huge opportunity
クラウド コンピューティングは大きなチャンスです
This whole thing keeps going
このすべてが続いていく
In fact, there is another huge opportunity
実はもう一つ大きなチャンスがあるんです
data science
データサイエンス
When you have so much data on it
大量のデータがある場合
if you study it hard
一生懸命勉強すれば
you will learn a lot
あなたはたくさんのことを学ぶでしょう
OK, what about the amount of data?
さて、データ量はどうでしょうか？
grow very, very energetic
成長得非常非常精能
everybody knows
誰もが知っている
OK various information
OK いろいろな情報
There are many types
種類非常的多
OK, some information is right and wrong
OK、情報によっては正しいものもあれば間違っているものもある
you don't know
あなたは知りません
Some might be fake anyway
とにかく偽物もあるかもしれない
some really are in there anyway
とにかく実際にそこにいる人もいます
OK so much information
OK、情報はたくさんあります
In fact, you start analyzing
実際に分析を始めると、
can start learning
学習を始めることができます
can do many things
たくさんのことができる
e.g. e-commerce
例：電子商取引
After a period of time
過一段時間
He knows what Guo Dawei likes to buy
彼は郭大偉が何を買うのが好きかを知っています
OK at night
夜でもOK
what should he sell
彼は何を売るべきか
OK that
わかりました
When is the time to sell him what?
彼に何を売る時期はいつですか？
Because of his family, which of his family members might buy those things?
彼の家族のせいで、彼の家族の誰がそれらのものを買うでしょうか?
He tried to sell you
彼はあなたを売ろうとしました
The same goes for medical care, with so many case files
医療も同様で、事件ファイルが非常に多い
he started to analyze
彼は分析を始めた
He said that Asians may be more prone to some diseases
彼は、アジア人はいくつかの病気にかかりやすいかもしれないと述べた
What might happen if you take some medicine
薬を飲むとどうなるか
So a lot of stuff started coming out
ということで、色々なものが出始めました
when manufacturing
製造時
I thought I had so many production materials
生産素材がたくさんあると思った
I can do analysis
分析ができる
For example, I can learn from many processes
たとえば、多くのプロセスから学ぶことができます
something went wrong i can do image processing
何か問題が発生しました。画像処理は可能です
See if there are any flaws in the things that are said to be made
自分の言ったことに間違いがないか確認する
I can see without human eyes
人間の目がなくても見える
It will be scanned automatically after a while
しばらくすると自動的にスキャンされます
this thing may be broken
これは壊れているかもしれない
Then you come to make further judgments
その後、あなたはさらに判断を下すようになります
social network life science
ソーシャルネットワークライフサイエンス
So new big opportunities start to appear
新たな大きなチャンスが現れ始める
Of course this is nothing
もちろんこれは何もない
Nothing compares to the fact that through all the computers
すべてのコンピュータを介して
through all internet
すべてのインターネットを通じて
Through all these apps and your phone
これらすべてのアプリと携帯電話を通じて
We're actually creating a gigantic machine
私たちは実際に巨大なマシンを作成しています
OK this huge machine is
OK、この巨大なマシンは
Including you and me we form a huge machine
あなたと私を含めて私たちは巨大な機械を形成します
What do you do when you don't know many things
知らないことがたくさんあるときはどうしますか
Go online and ask, there is always someone who knows, right?
ネットにアクセスして聞いてみれば、必ず知っている人がいるでしょう？
gather everyone's wisdom
みんなの知恵を集めて
thus becoming a gigantic machine
こうして巨大な機械になる
This machine is made up of people and all the machine software
この機械は人間とすべての機械ソフトウェアで構成されています
OK this is a
OK、これは
I'm afraid it's the biggest machine in the world.
恐れ入りますが、それは世界最大の機械です。
OK is made of all of us
OKは私たち全員でできています
OK good
いいよ
After that there are these great
その後には、これらの素晴らしいものがあります
These attractive these so-called this
これらの魅力的なこれらのいわゆるこれ
Be it data science or cloud computing
データサイエンスでもクラウドコンピューティングでも
Great smartphone too
スマホもすごいよ
is the world so good
世界はそんなに良いのか
Actually it's not, right?
実際にはそうではありませんよね？
The world is getting scarier, right?
世界はますます怖くなっていますよね？
He's not the only one who knows me too well
私のことをよく知っているのは彼だけではない
And things including mine are too easy to get lost
そして私のものも含めて物はあまりにも簡単に紛失してしまう
Right, like I mentioned to you guys
そう、先ほども言ったように、
Is your cellphone safe
あなたの携帯電話は安全ですか
wake up a little in the morning
朝少し起きて
What to do if your phone won't turn on
携帯電話の電源が入らない場合の対処方法
If one day I mention to you
いつかあなたにそのことを話したら
You need to check Guo Dawei's phone number
Guo Dawei の電話番号を確認する必要があります
Wow, the address book is gone
うわ、アドレス帳消えた
My photos from the past 20 years have disappeared
過去20年間の写真が消えてしまいました
what to do
何をすべきか
phone is not safe
電話は安全ではありません
You don't think your phone is safe
自分の携帯電話が安全だとは思っていない
like your pc
あなたのPCのように
it is not safe
安全ではありません
There are all kinds of malicious programs running on it
あらゆる種類の悪意のあるプログラムが実行されています
and more and more
そしてますます
Everyone said, would it be safer for me to use a mobile phone from a certain manufacturer?
誰もが「特定のメーカーの携帯電話を使用した方が安全でしょうか？」と言いました。
won't
しません
Anyway, some people are using it, and some people want to destroy it.
とにかく、それを使用している人もいれば、それを破壊したい人もいます。
so there must be
だからあるはずだ
so what happens
それで何が起こるか
on your computer, it happens on your phone
あなたのコンピュータでも、それはあなたの携帯電話でも起こります
Someone will collect your sensitive information
誰かがあなたの機密情報を収集するでしょう
it will hack your phone
それはあなたの携帯電話をハッキングするでしょう
like hacking a computer
コンピューターをハッキングするような
What about the phone? Some malicious programs?
電話や悪意のあるプログラムについてはどうですか?
will draw your personal information
あなたの個人情報を引き出します
even make phone calls for you, right?
電話をかけてもいいですよね？
Let you send text messages to friends you haven't seen for a long time
長い間会っていない友人にテキスト メッセージを送信できます
that it exists in a different way
違う形で存在しているということ
it could be some code way
それは何らかのコードの方法かもしれません
It is possible to go to the edge of the net to view a web page
ネットの端に行ってWebページを閲覧することが可能
Just like you go online with a computer, you will be poisoned
コンピューターでオンラインに接続するのと同じように、中毒になります
OK so this thing will happen
OK、これは起こります
like your pc
あなたのPCのように
Your phone will have these too
あなたの携帯電話にもこれらがあります
For example, something like a worm
たとえば、虫のようなもの
This bug-like software
このバグのようなソフトウェア
It basically takes pictures on your phone
基本的にはスマホで写真を撮ります
it just keeps on copying
それはコピーを続けるだけです
Find a way to run to another phone
別の電話にアクセスする方法を見つける
Its purpose is not to steal your stuff
その目的はあなたのものを盗むことではありません
just run on it
ただその上を走るだけ
In fact, it makes it happy
実際、それは幸せになります
But your phone is getting slower and slower
でも、携帯電話の速度はどんどん遅くなっていきます
Because there are still some bugs running on it
まだバグが残っているので
because it also runs the shake time
シェイクタイムも実行されるため
so slow you down
だから遅くする
more than that
それ以上
Many people will steal your personal information
多くの人があなたの個人情報を盗みます
or even pawn your computer
またはコンピュータを質入れすることさえできます
collect your information
自分の情報を収集する
Or send you an advertisement if you have nothing to do
何もすることがない場合は広告を送ります
still can't press
まだ押せない
So all sorts of things are showing up
そうするといろんなものが現れてくるんです
Agents refer to these malicious programs that collect your sensitive data
エージェントは、機密データを収集するこれらの悪意のあるプログラムを指します。
What he said is your Trojan horse program
彼が言ったのはあなたのトロイの木馬プログラムです
just run into your place
ただあなたの場所に駆け込んでください
Then remotely control your mobile phone
次に、携帯電話をリモート制御します
Of course it's the so-called milkworm
もちろんいわゆるミルクワームです
Just in the back, just walking
ただ後ろで、ただ歩くだけ
all these things
これらすべてのこと
Or like you guys on a normal computer
または、通常のコンピュータを使用している皆さんのように
There is a so-called cookie bar
いわゆるクッキーバーがあります
Everyone knows that when you use a browser to view something
ブラウザを使用して何かを表示すると、誰もがそれを知っています。
Sometimes when you switch to different pages
時々、別のページに切り替えたとき
he knows you're still yours
彼はあなたがまだあなたのものであることを知っています
why does he know it's you
なぜ彼はそれがあなただと知っているのですか
Because he wrote in some materials they sent
彼らが送った資料に彼はこう書いていたから
Where the data is placed is placed in the so-called cookie
データがどこに配置されるかは、いわゆる Cookie に配置されます。
Since cookies can be placed in cookies
クッキーはクッキーの中に入れることができるので
can steal from the cookie, right?
クッキーから盗めるんですよね？
so what about these things
それで、これらのことはどうですか
Cookie refers to some data stored in the browser
Cookieとは、ブラウザに保存されている一部のデータを指します
let the site send something
サイトに何かを送信させましょう
Of course there are a lot of personal information in it.
もちろんその中には個人情報も多く含まれています。
Actually he could steal it
実際、彼はそれを盗むことができた
OK so a lot of things to steal
OK、盗むものはたくさんあります
OK everybody say
OK、みんな言います
that is a personal computer but
それはパソコンですが、
Everyone is not
誰もがそうではありません
this was a while ago
これは少し前のことです
done a collection of data
データ収集を完了しました
Of course it's okay for you to drink a bit
もちろん少しくらい飲んでも大丈夫ですよ
You see, in 2014 alone, there were already 650,000 malicious layers
2014 年だけでも、すでに 650,000 の悪意のあるレイヤーが存在していました。
a lot right?
たくさんありますよね？
Everyone, of course don't guess
もちろんあなたは推測しないでしょう
Don't doubt that there is more now
今はもっとたくさんあることを疑わないでください
Well, everyone, these malicious levels have been installed many times.
皆さん、これらの悪意のあるレベルは何度もインストールされています。
it's just that you don't know
それはあなたが知らないだけです
We need some way to help us analyze
分析に役立つ何らかの方法が必要です
help us interpret
解釈を手伝ってください
can help us troubleshoot these problems
これらの問題のトラブルシューティングに役立ちます
So we need some powerful way
したがって、何らかの強力な方法が必要です
come to analyze
分析しに来てください
And the current attack is not like the previous attack
そして、現在の攻撃は前の攻撃とは異なります
right on your phone
携帯電話ですぐに
where it may attack you from several points together
複数の地点から同時に攻撃される可能性がある場所
or from here to overweight far overweight
またはここからはるかに太り過ぎの太り過ぎへ
Let's attack your phone or your system together
一緒にあなたの携帯電話やシステムを攻撃しましょう
So your analysis also won't be analyzed on the same machine
したがって、分析も同じマシン上では分析されません。
You will collect a lot of information on the Internet
インターネットでたくさんの情報を集めることになります
look where it's coming from
それがどこから来ているか見てください
then you have to defend your job
それなら自分の仕事を守らなければならない
If this is knocked out, it must be able to make up for it.
これがノックアウトされても、それを補うことができるはずです。
So this thing becomes more and more complicated
したがって、この問題はますます複雑になります
What do you say
あなたは何を言っていますか
It's the rest of the world's business not mine
それは私の仕事ではなく、世界の残りの部分です
Ladies and gentlemen, let me report to you that Taiwan is actually very dangerous.
皆さん、台湾は実はとても危険だということをご報告させていただきます。
This is the whole world they do a ranking
これが世界全体で彼らはランキングを行っています
Which telecom operators are the worst?
どの通信事業者が最悪ですか?
OK everyone, the second place is Chunghwa Telecom
さて皆さん、2位は中華電信です
OK ok it's 2013 of course we hope he improves
OK、OK、もう 2013 年です、もちろん彼が改善することを願っています
OK, but actually, let me show you one more
OK、でも実はもう一つお見せしましょう
There is another miserable thing, you said that the problem of Chunghwa Telecom does not dare us to try
もう一つ悲惨なことがあります。中華電信の問題は我々が挑戦する勇気がないと言いました。
Guys, this is another one, this is another survey
皆さん、これは別の調査です、これは別の調査です
In fact, comment control is that he manipulates your computer remotely
実際、コメント制御とは、リモートであなたのコンピュータを操作することです。
OK, of course it means that your computer has been hacked.
もちろん、それはあなたのコンピュータがハッキングされたことを意味します。
Sorry, we are number two in the world OK
申し訳ありませんが、私たちは世界第 2 位です。
Well, of course it's great.
まあ、もちろん素晴らしいですよ。
Ours is not only the top, we are the top three OK
僕らはトップだけじゃない、トップ3でもOK
Well Taiwan is a very interesting environment
そうですね、台湾はとても興味深い環境です
Everyone come over here and play it OK
みんなここに来て遊んでOK
So it's actually very, very dangerous OK
つまり、実際には非常に危険です
All of our stuff is constantly being infected and attacked.
私たちのすべてのものは常に感染し、攻撃されています。
ok then of course i have so far
わかりました、もちろんこれまでのところはあります
What did I tell you?
私はあなたに何を言いましたか？
I'll talk to you about the phone
携帯電話についてお話します
like i told you guys
私が皆さんに言ったように
cell phone is actually
携帯電話は実は
it represents a world
それは世界を表します
just like
と同じように
Of course the mobile phone is very important, right?
もちろん携帯電話はとても重要ですよね？
I saw a while ago
少し前に見た
I saw one two days ago
2日前にも見たよ
a report on tv
テレビのレポート
Even he speaks on the Internet
彼もインターネット上で発言している
He said if your girlfriend
彼は言った、もしあなたのガールフレンドが
fell into the water with your phone
携帯電話ごと水に落ちた
Please save the water first
まずは水を貯めてください
Many people will think a little bit
少しは思う人も多いだろう
Then of course you're in trouble, right?
そうすると当然困りますよね？
It will be bad if your girlfriend finds out about you
あなたのガールフレンドにあなたのことが知られたら大変なことになります
but what does it mean
しかしそれはどういう意味ですか
The mobile phone is really inseparable from it, right?
携帯電話は本当に切っても切れない関係ですよね。
think about it
考えてみてください
In fact, we just mentioned
実際、先ほども触れましたが、
mobile phone
携帯電話
It actually brings us to a
それは実際に私たちに次のようなことをもたらします。
something special
何か特別なもの
it's not a phone anymore
それはもう電話ではありません
it's a smart phone
それはスマートフォンです
it represents a huge ecosystem
それは巨大な生態系を表します
behind the cloud
雲の後ろに
Provide various services
さまざまなサービスを提供する
and through this phone
そしてこの電話を通して
have seen the whole world
全世界を見てきた
Of course my phone is not safe
もちろん私の携帯電話は安全ではありません
In this process, there are actually many new
この過程で、実際には多くの新しいものが生まれます
ice opportunity presents itself
アイスチャンスが訪れる
whatever on your phone
携帯電話で何でも
or somewhere else
または他の場所で
In fact, the world behind
実は背後の世界は
bigger than your phone
携帯電話より大きい
there are clouds behind you
あなたの後ろには雲があります
you have all kinds of services
あらゆる種類のサービスがあります
you have different scientific operations
さまざまな科学的操作を行っています
in the whole back
背中全体に
They actually form a
彼らは実際に
a huge ecosystem on top
頂上には巨大な生態系がある
of course
もちろん
everyone knows
みんな知ってる
his whole thing
彼のすべて
won't stop at this point
この時点では止まらない
In fact, we will soon be in the context of the next era
実際、私たちはもうすぐ次の時代に突入します
That is the so-called new era of interconnectedness
それがいわゆる相互接続の新時代です
A new era where everything is connected
すべてがつながる新時代
We all know the Internet of Things
モノのインターネットについては誰もが知っています
everything has to be connected
すべてが接続されなければなりません
including your mobile device
モバイルデバイスを含む
unfortunately including your car
残念ながらあなたの車も含めて
include your building
あなたの建物を含めてください
All sorts of things all strung together
いろんなものが絡み合って
I can't see this word anymore
もうこの言葉は見えない
Soon they estimated 50 B Company
すぐに彼らは 50 社の B 社を見積もりました。
50 billion things
50個10億的東西
to break again
また壊れる
I can't see it now
今は見えない
all connected
すべてつながっている
everything is connected
すべてはつながっている
The car is going up too
車も上がってます
Of course, no one will doubt this matter.
もちろん、この件について疑う人はいないだろう。
right
右
Because in fact, there have been many reports about this matter.
実際、この件に関しては多くの報道がなされているからです。
When the machine is in the next fifth generation of 5G computer
マシンが次の第 5 世代 5G コンピュータの場合
In fact, what we have to deal with is the network that the machine is connected to.
実際、私たちが対処しなければならないのは、マシンが接続されているネットワークです。
So the amount of data generated by machines will start to surpass
したがって、マシンによって生成されるデータの量は超え始めるでしょう
The amount of data people are using to communicate
人々が通信に使用するデータ量
In 5G, it is actually one of the important goals.
5G では、これは実際に重要な目標の 1 つです。
Of course these things have a purpose
もちろんこれらには目的があります
Why we need IoT
なぜIoTが必要なのか
need these things
これらのものが必要です
In fact, a very important purpose is that we
実際、非常に重要な目的は、
longing for a smart life
スマートな生活への憧れ
We have a smart environment
当社にはスマートな環境があります
We can have a good one control at home
自宅で優れたワンコントロールを実現できます
The air conditioner was already on when you got home
家に帰ったらもうエアコンがついていた
when you walk too close to the tv
テレビに近づきすぎると
I want you to stand back a little
少し下がってほしい
OK
OK
then you get in the car
それから車に乗ります
In the car, you just tell him
車の中で彼に言うだけです
I want to go to Academia Sinica
中央研究院に行きたい
Hey, then drive to Academia Sinica
ねえ、それでは中央研究院へ車で行ってください
ok
Ok
Hey, it sounds like
ねえ、それは次のように聞こえます
very far away
とても遠くにある
In fact it's getting closer
実際、それは近づいています
ok everyone will see
オーケー、みんなが見るだろう
Google's self-driving car
Googleの自動運転車
Apple spends a lot of money
Appleは多額の金を使っている
everybody is doing these things
誰もがこれらのことをやっています
Something has begun to creep in on your new
あなたの新しいものに何かが忍び込み始めています
started appearing in the car
車の中に現れ始めた
What is included
含まれるもの
i forgot which year
何年か忘れた
The report says 2018
報告書には2018年とある
He said that Toyota can do many cars
彼はトヨタは多くの車を作ることができると言いました
so-called distance-controlled collision avoidance
いわゆる距離制御型衝突回避
ok
Ok
So he's already started going in that direction.
つまり、彼はすでにその方向に進み始めています。
Your car has already started to go in the direction of intelligence
あなたの車はすでにインテリジェンスの方向へ進み始めています
Soon your car might be like a cell phone
もうすぐあなたの車は携帯電話のようになるかもしれません
ok
Ok
that's not all
それがすべてではありません
Do many people use these
多くの人がこれを使っていますか
so-called this
いわゆるこれ
wearable device
ウェアラブルデバイス
measure your sales
売上を測定する
ok know how much you walked today
さて、今日どれだけ歩いたか知っていますか
ok
Ok
of course
もちろん
not just selling wave
波を売るだけではない
still look at your heartbeat
まだあなたの鼓動を見てください
ah many many others
ああ、他にもたくさん
ok you today
はい、今日はあなた
Can help you do a lot of statistics
多くの統計を行うのに役立ちます
analyze
分析
OK
OK
So what about wearables?
では、ウェアラブルについてはどうでしょうか?
will appear in large numbers
大量に現れるだろう
Now, everyone only sees the watch
今では誰もが時計しか見ていない
And this wrist device on your hand
そしてあなたの手にあるこのリストデバイス
But soon a lot of things will come in
でもすぐに色々なものが入ってくるよ
including with
を含む
It has something to do with your life support
それはあなたの生命維持に関係しています
what's inside you
あなたの中には何があるのか
what you wear
あなたが着てるもの
These things will start to appear one after another.
こういったものが次々と現れ始めます。
OK
OK
So actually we're starting to usher in a new era
実際、私たちは新しい時代を迎え始めています
But of course you all know
でも、もちろん皆さんご存知ですよね
Everyone has seen this photo, right?
皆さんもこんな写真を見たことがあるのではないでしょうか？
Everyone's waiting for something but everyone's looking at their phone
みんな何かを待っているけど、みんな携帯を見ている
right
右
It seems that you have seen similar photos, right?
似たような写真を見たことがありますよね？
Everyone got this job, got this job
誰もがこの仕事に就き、この仕事に就いた
after this MRT
このMRTの後
Is it like this for everyone?
みんなもこんな感じでしょうか？
OK
OK
including myself too, right?
私も含めてですよね？
everyone is skating
みんなスケートしてる
OK
OK
The family seems to be slipping while sitting at the dining table
家族がダイニングテーブルに座っているときに滑ってしまったようです
That
それか
Fewer people talking in restaurants
レストランで話す人が減った
OK everyone is typing
OK、みんな入力中です
OK, tell people how delicious my food is, take Zhang Xiang and give it away, right?
よし、私の食べ物がどれほどおいしいかを人々に伝えて、張祥を連れて行って配ってみませんか？
Well, actually, we already have a new time.
さて、実際には、すでに新しい時間があります。
this habit
この習慣
And the kid seems to be starting to skateboard too.
そしてその子もスケートボードを始めているようです。
OK, a lot of things have changed, right?
OK、多くのことが変わりましたね?
The car is also starting to be connected to the Internet, and it will be here soon
車もインターネットに接続され始めており、もうすぐ登場します
Is your TV not the same as before?
あなたのテレビは以前と同じではありませんか？
your smart tv this show you watch
あなたのスマートテレビ あなたが見ているこの番組
It seems that it is not only local programs
ローカル番組だけではないようです
In fact, our new habit
実際、私たちの新しい習慣は
have begun to emerge in our time
私たちの時代にも現れ始めています
Or even when I was a child, or what you imagine
あるいは私が子供の頃でさえ、あるいはあなたが想像していることでも
It's actually not the same in the next era.
実際、次の時代も同じではありません。
how do you talk to each other
お互いにどのように話しますか
how do you use something
何かをどうやって使うのですか
In fact, it's not the same. OK
実際には、同じではありません。
So actually what I'm going to say is
それで、実際に私が言おうとしているのは、
Mobile phones are not just mobile phones.
携帯電話は単なる携帯電話ではありません。
Mobile phones are our window to the world
携帯電話は世界への窓です
OK let's go through it
さて、それではやってみましょう
see a lot of new things
たくさんの新しいものを見る
And the whole story isn't just about the phone.
そして、この話は電話だけに関するものではありません。
Cloud from behind Service from behind
背後からのクラウド 背後からのサービス
The so-called science of data, the whole of it
いわゆるデータの科学、その全体
underpins an idea of ​​what we call the smartphone
私たちがスマートフォンと呼ぶものの概念を支えています
So through mobile phones and other communication devices?
では、携帯電話やその他の通信デバイスを介して?
I'm like I just mentioned to you guys
先ほど皆さんに話したような気がします
In fact, we humans have formed a
実際、私たち人間は
a huge new machine
巨大な新しい機械
We have new and different ways to share our knowledge
私たちは知識を共有するための新しいさまざまな方法を持っています
We also have an unprecedented way of communicating
私たちはまた、これまでにないコミュニケーション方法を持っています
you now in some way
あなたは今、何らかの形で
you can put your thoughts in no time
すぐに自分の考えをまとめることができます
soon maybe take a walk to africa
近いうちにアフリカまで散歩してみようかな
was not possible before
以前は不可能だった
Now everything is chained together
今、すべてがひとつに連鎖している
as if everyone is always saying
まるでみんながいつも言ってるかのように
how many times do you jump
何回ジャンプしますか
say six times you can
6回言ってください
Can meet everyone in the world
世界中のみんなに会える
this was not possible before
これは以前は不可能でした
Of course you say
もちろんあなたは言います
can i resist this thing
これに抵抗してもいいですか
Let me tell you, don't resist
言っておきますが、抵抗しないでください
give you a few examples
いくつか例を挙げてください
Recall everyone
みんなを思い出してください
The great things that have happened in the past fifty years
過去50年間に起こった素晴らしい出来事
personal computer
パソコン
appeared about forty or fifty years ago
およそ40年か50年前に登場した
what did the advent of the personal computer create
パーソナルコンピュータの出現は何を生み出したのか
It was called IBM PC and so on, which appeared at the beginning
IBM PCなどと呼ばれるもので、最初に登場したのがこの種類です
Of course, it also created our IT industry in Taiwan.
もちろん、台湾のIT産業もそれによって生まれました。
OK
OK
Of course, you can also say the other way around, who misses this opportunity?
もちろん、逆のことも言えます。この機会を逃す人はいないでしょうか。
Then the Internet
それからインターネット
The so-called Internet of physics begins to appear
いわゆる物理学のインターネットが出現し始める
Of course it makes a huge difference
もちろんそれは大きな違いを生みます
then you ask who is hurting on this
それからあなたはこれで誰が傷ついているのか尋ねます
After the beginning of the so-called Internet
いわゆるインターネットが始まってから
How many people still write letters?
今でも手紙を書いている人はどれくらいいるでしょうか？
few people write letters anymore
もう手紙を書く人はほとんどいません
Send email to everyone
全員にメールを送信
OK
OK
ok so start changing
オーケー、それでは変化を始めましょう
Then came the so-called WallWideWeb
その後、いわゆる WallwideWeb が登場しました。
The so-called HTTP
所謂HTTP
I can get the data started by
データの取得を開始するには、
Web page started sending
Webページの配信を開始しました
OK
OK
You start to think about what has changed
何が変わったのか考え始める
so-called browser
いわゆるブラウザ
OK
OK
How do you share your data?
データをどのように共有しますか?
has changed
変更されました
you no longer use your stuff
もう自分のものを使わなくなった
pass it on or copy it to others
他の人に渡すかコピーする
Once on this so-called portal site
このいわゆるポータルサイトにアクセスすると
Immediately all went out for a walk
すぐにみんなで散歩に出かけました
people who didn't keep up
ついていけない人たち
It's like night training is right
夜のトレーニングが正しいようです
when searches start coming up
検索が出始めたら
Who caught up and who didn't catch up
誰が追いついて、誰が追いつけなかったのか
created the emergence of Google and other companies
Google やその他の企業の出現を生み出した
Then mobile devices started showing up
その後、モバイルデバイスが登場し始めました
There are many companies that have not caught up
追いついてない会社もたくさんある
thus lagging behind, say, Intel
したがって、たとえばインテルに遅れをとっている
In this, it has lost a lot to companies like Arm
この点で、Armのような企業に多くを失った
Why because he doesn't know about this huge change
なぜかというと、彼はこの大きな変化を知らないからです。
his past great success
彼の過去の大成功
become a huge hindrance to him now
今では彼にとって大きな障害となっている
Clouds start to appear
雲が現れ始める
Of course we can guess
もちろん推測できます
Now this company is like Google, Amazon
今ではこの会社はGoogleやAmazonのようなものです
The company is up
会社は元気になった
Which companies will start to cloud weak
どの企業が弱者のクラウド化を開始するか
So actually what I'm going to say is
それで、実際に私が言おうとしているのは、
This era is actually moving forward
この時代は実は進んでいる
keep going
立ち止まるな
Then we may not be able to resist it
そうしたら、私たちはそれに抵抗できないかもしれません
But we can put it to good use
しかし、それを有効に活用することはできます
Then we must welcome the era where everything is connected
そして、すべてがつながる時代を迎えなければなりません
this is my hope
これが私の希望です
one day if i could wear it
いつかそれを着ることができたら
such an internet of things
そのようなモノのインターネット
such a device
そのような装置
this is what i want most
これが私が一番欲しいものです
But I don't know if I can wait
でも待てるか分からない
Finally I thank the slideshow
最後にスライドショーに感謝します
many people offer me some help
多くの人が私に助けを申し出てくれます
Including Professor Huang Yanlan
黄燕蘭教授を含む
Professor Hong Shao
ホン・シャオ教授
Professor Luo Wenfeng
羅文豐教授
Professor Huo Bicheng
ヒュー・ビチェン
Professor Zhang Yuanhao
張元豪教授
And Dr. Yang Chuanyue
そしてヤン・チュアンユエ博士
Professor Zhang Zhewei
張哲維教授
with Professor Huang Bojun
ファン・ボジュン教授と
I'll report it here
ここで報告させていただきます
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
thank you very much
どうもありがとうございます
I have benefited a lot
たくさんの恩恵を受けました
I believe that everyone here has also benefited a lot.
ここにいる皆さんも大きな恩恵を受けたと思います。
do you want to take a break or
休みたいですか、それとも
it doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
Okay, let's see if there is anything else we need to ask
はい、他に何か質問があるか見てみましょう
please
お願いします
Hello, what I mentioned in the speech just now is
こんにちは、先ほどのスピーチで私が話したのは、
data science or so-called data scientists
データサイエンス、いわゆるデータサイエンティスト
As far as my own understanding is
私自身の理解している限りでは
I think he should also be classified as a basic subject
彼も基礎科目に分類されるべきだと思います
The foundation grows Betal Size
基礎長得Betal Size
It should still be about how to use these basic disciplines
やはり重要なのは、これらの基本的な規律をどのように活用するかということです。
So what I want to ask is to tell you what you think
それで私が聞きたいのは、あなたがどう思うかということです
What do you think a so-called data scientist
いわゆるデータサイエンティストはどう思いますか
What basic disciplines did he use
彼はどのような基本的な訓練を行ったのか
Then how does he use it
では彼はそれをどうやって使うのか
or what proportion to use the knowledge of these subjects
またはこれらの主題の知識をどの程度の割合で使用するか
Then he compared our current existing traditional fields
そして彼は、現在の既存の伝統的な畑を比較しました。
such as physical chemistry psychology
物理化学心理学など
Or what is the difference between a mathematician and a statistician?
あるいは数学者と統計学者の違いは何でしょうか?
Thanks
ありがとう
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
Data Science is actually a very
データサイエンスは実際には非常に重要です
sex name ok
性人的名字 ok
Represents a group of things
物事のグループを表します
What about data science?
データサイエンスについてはどうですか?
In fact, it itself is a cross-field thing
実際、それ自体は分野を超えたものです
when i talk about data science
データサイエンスについて話すとき
the question you should ask me is where is it used
あなたが私に尋ねるべき質問は、それがどこで使われているかということです
ok if you use it in the so-called manufacturing
わかりました、いわゆる製造業で使用する場合はどうなりますか
At this time, the experts on the manufacturing side must come in together
このとき、製造側の専門家が力を合わせなければなりません。
ok then when you ask me
わかりました、それではあなたが私に尋ねたら
Is this data science applied in medical treatment?
このデータサイエンスは医療にも応用されるのでしょうか？
The medical experts have to come in together.
医療専門家が協力しなければなりません。
then you will notice
そうすればあなたは気づくでしょう
What is included in data science?
データサイエンスには何が含まれますか?
That is to say, analyzing these data
つまり、これらのデータを分析すると、
These scientists who sorted out these capabilities
これらの機能を分類した科学者
In addition, there are also experts in the application direction of certain fields
さらに、特定の分野のアプリケーションの方向性に関する専門家もいます
after putting it together
組み立てた後
to produce truly useful data science
本当に役立つデータサイエンスを生み出すために
So so overall
全体的にまあまあ
In fact, if we look at it academically
実は学術的に見てみると
In fact, it will be composed from different angles
実際には、さまざまな角度から構成されます
There are some words from this information project
この情報プロジェクトからの言葉がいくつかあります
such expertise comes in
そのような専門知識が入ってくる
Of course, it's not just data analysis.
もちろん、データ分析だけではありません。
or materials for learning such techniques
またはそのような技術を学ぶための教材
If data analysis Data learning techniques
データ分析なら データ学習手法
Much of it is in computer science
その多くはコンピューターサイエンスに関するものです
There is a part of this following technique
このテクニックの一部には次のようなものがあります
is on mathematics
数学中です
there's a lot of knowledge about that
それについてはたくさんの知識があります
In fact, in different application directions
実際、さまざまな用途の方向で
OK so that's about all I can say
OK、私が言えるのはこれくらいです
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
Since we are talking about wisdom
知恵の話をしているので、
Speaking of the largest machine
最大の機械といえば
Speaking of Sharing
共有といえば
Then such words
するとそんな言葉が
What are the places where people can't be replaced?
人の代わりがいない場所はどこですか？
any thoughts on this
これについて何か考えはありますか
can share with us
私たちと共有できます
Thanks
ありがとう
good
良い
that's an interesting question
それは興味深い質問です
If the machine is so powerful
マシンがそんなに強力なら
Then what should we humans play?
では、私たち人間は何をすればいいのでしょうか？
what kind of role
どのような役割ですか
OK good
いいよ
Fortunately, there are still many roles to play.
幸いなことに、果たすべき役割はまだたくさんあります。
OK
OK
But you can imagine
しかし、あなたは想像することができます
There are a lot of characters starting to disappear
どんどん消えていくキャラが多い
Can you tell me which characters have disappeared now?
現在消えてしまったキャラクターを教えていただけますか？
You've noticed that some jobs in the bank are starting to disappear.
銀行の一部の仕事がなくなり始めていることに気づきました。
You often use ATM machines
ATMをよく利用します
you are not very expensive
あなたはそれほど高価ではありません
Some people are not very smart to do some materials
一部の資料を作成するのがあまり賢くない人もいます
Do account processing
アカウント処理を行う
OK the way you buy a ticket has changed
チケットの購入方法が変わりました
Some parts of the semantic set are starting to disappear
セマンティックセットの一部が消え始めている
OK
OK
But there are many creative directions
しかし、創造的な方向性はたくさんあります
Or new jobs are starting to emerge
あるいは新しい仕事が生まれ始めている
So what I'm going to say is
それで、私が言いたいのは、
indeed in the process
確かにその過程で
The computer starts to treat some of us
コンピューターが私たちの一部を治療し始める
regular
通常
simplified work
簡素化された作業
jobs that can be easily analyzed
簡単に分析できるジョブ
Structured work begins to displace
構造化された仕事が置き換えられ始める
But it is actually to some extent
でも実際はある程度そうなんです
It also creates something new
それはまた新しいものを生み出します
then of course you can talk
それならもちろん話せます
Are the jobs created
雇用は創出されていますか
$ less than the jobs that are currently disappearing
現在失われつつある仕事よりも $ 少ない
currently in many ways yes
現在、多くの点ではい
OK
OK
you can see
見ることができます
Today I have automation
今日は自動化を導入しました
In fact, many jobs in factories are starting to disappear.
実際、工場では多くの仕事が失われ始めています。
because I can automate
自動化できるから
And it's actually more efficient doing something
そして、実際には何かをする方が効率的です
but you will find
でもあなたは見つけます
many things
たくさんのこと
you still have to ask someone to do it
まだ誰かに頼まなければなりません
OK
OK
For example, I mentioned to you
たとえば、先ほどもお話しましたが、
let me give you an example
例をあげましょう
Let's say I want to design something
何かをデザインしたいとします
like a cup
カップのように
these grips
これらのグリップ
all these things
これらすべてのこと
In fact, many things are still done by people.
実際、多くのことは今でも人間によって行われています。
what about the computer
コンピューターはどうですか
In fact, far from the wisdom of real people
実際、現実の人々の知恵とは程遠い
There is still a big gap
まだ大きなギャップがあります
Of course we think it's great
もちろん私たちはそれが素晴らしいと思っています
but it's still far
でもまだ遠い
OK
OK
let me give you an example
例をあげましょう
Now everyone is always talking
今ではみんないつも話してます
I'm from a photo
私は写真から来ました
I hope to be able to identify
特定できるといいですね
is there a cat in it
その中に猫がいますか
or is there a dog laughing in it
それともその中で犬が笑っていますか
OK
OK
Well guys it's very easy for each of us
そうですね、私たち一人一人にとってそれはとても簡単です
As soon as you see it, you'll know if anyone is in there this time.
見たらすぐに、今度は誰かがそこにいるかどうかがわかります
You can tell if he's laughing or crying, right?
彼が笑っているのか泣いているのかわかりますよね？
But it is very difficult for a computer
でも、コンピュータではとても難しいのです
OK
OK
Although many people still do some so-called Deep Learning technologies
多くの人が依然としていわゆるディープラーニング技術を行っていますが、
Deep Learning These technologies are basically the last two stages
ディープラーニング これらのテクノロジーは基本的に最後の 2 段階です
The first stage is a bit like the so-called Filtering stage
最初のステージは、いわゆるフィルタリングステージに似ています。
Just how to abstract the data inside and extract it
内部のデータを抽象化して抽出する方法
turn it into something else
それを別のものに変える
Then do the comparison
それから比較してみます
Let's see if the answer is
答えがどうか見てみましょう
So in the process you will find it very interesting that is to say
その過程で、とても興味深いことに気づくでしょう。
Now you will find that there are some research findings that say
さて、次のような研究結果があることがわかります。
It seems to work. I don’t know why.
効果があるようですが、理由はわかりません。
so what i want to say is
だから私が言いたいのは
As simple as that, is there a dog smiling in a photo?
単純なことですが、写真の中で犬が笑っているでしょうか？
It's hard for a computer
パソコンって難しいですね
It's very simple for us humans
私たちにとってはとても簡単なことです
OK so I'm back to these questions
さて、これらの質問に戻ります
we are inside
私たちは中にいます
There will always be many, many roles in it
そこには常にたくさんの役割が存在するでしょう
It's just that we'll find out
それは私たちが知ることになるだけです
We'll become a complementary character with him
私たちは彼と補完的なキャラクターになります
an interactive character
インタラクティブなキャラクター
more and more like this
ますますこのように
so many things will disappear
とても多くのものが消えてしまうだろう
But there are many things that will be born
でも、これから生まれるものもたくさんある
that's how i feel
それが私の気持ちです
Hello Professor Guo
郭教授好
I feel very rewarded today
今日はとてもやりがいを感じています
thank you for a great day
素晴らしい一日をありがとう
My name is Lin Yuxuan
私の名前は林玉軒です
own background as a psychiatrist
自身の精神科医としての経歴
Also an amateur mobile app developer
アマチュアのモバイルアプリ開発者でもあります
So I would like to ask Professor Guo two questions
そこで郭教授に2つの質問をしたいと思います。
One is from the perspective of a psychiatrist
一つは精神科医の視点から
The other is asking from a mobile development perspective
もう 1 つはモバイル開発の観点からの質問です
That Nature is the journal of nature
Nature は自然の日記であるということ
There was a report of a cause two weeks ago
2週間前に原因の報告がありました
Reports say that all
報告によると、すべて
mental health
メンタルヘルスに応用される
All apps for psychiatry
精神科用のすべてのアプリ
Call Pocket Spirit to make
Pocket Spirit に電話して作成してください
Pocket Psychiatrist
ポケット精神科医
then i believe
それなら私は信じます
I think what the professor just said is very correct
今先生がおっしゃったことはとても正しいと思います
Which means the phone has completely changed
つまり、電話機が完全に変わったということです
our new way of life
私たちの新しい生活様式
Then I think the phone does
それなら電話でもいいと思います
His new technology also changed
彼の新しい技術も変化した
human psychology and behavior
人間の心理と行動
then i want to ask
それから聞きたいです
If it is from the perspective of teaching you
教えるという観点から言えば
and your point of view
そしてあなたの視点
user experience and user interface
ユーザーエクスペリエンスとユーザーインターフェース
Research in the process of mobile app development
モバイルアプリ開発中のリサーチ
heavy or not
重不重要
This is the first question
これが最初の質問です
Because human behavior may be changing all the time
人間の行動は常に変化している可能性があるため、
The second is to say
2つ目は、こう言うことです
The main content just taught
今教えてもらった主な内容
Is introducing some architecture of Android
Android のいくつかのアーキテクチャを導入しています
That Android it from this 4.1 4.2
Android はこれ 4.1 4.2 から
There is a big breakthrough
大きな進歩があります
and now to 6.0
そして今は6.0へ
Then what we have been more worried about is that
それから、私たちがもっと心配しているのは、
Because of my doctoral dissertation in the past
過去に博士論文を書いたことがきっかけで
It is a service to write the background of the cell-phone
携帯電話の背景を書き込むサービスです
to detect some human behavior
人間の行動を検出するため
Then we actually all have a worry
そうするとみんな心配になるんです
Worried that Android is in
Android が入っているのではないかと心配
while it's progressing it will look like
進行中は次のようになります
The iOS system may put many parts of the background
iOS システムは背景の多くの部分を配置する場合があります
get it out of our reach
私たちの手の届かないところに置いてください
Then I want to ask the professor to read this
それから教授にこれを読んでもらいたいのですが
A process of Android's development
Androidの開発プロセス
Yes, because now it's like the professor said
そう、今は教授の言う通りだから
In fact, the protection of information security is very important
実際、情報セキュリティの保護は非常に重要です
I don't know what the professor thinks about this safety
教授がこの安全性についてどう考えているかは分かりません
There is also a disease that develops between the two
二人の間に発症する病気もある
ok let me answer the first question first
さて、最初の質問に答えさせてください
That is to say, a study of the user interface
つまりユーザーインターフェースの研究です
It's definitely very important OK
それは間違いなく非常に重要です、OK
Now everyone's most criticized
今、誰もが最も批判されているのは、
For example, a mobile phone is also good
例えば携帯電話でもいいです
or wearing a taxi or your watch
タクシーに乗ったり、時計を着けたり
OK, everyone thinks why the watch consumes so much power
OK、時計がなぜそんなに多くの電力を消費するのか誰もが考えます
You bring your smartwatch now
今すぐスマートウォッチをご持参ください
why so much power consumption
なぜそんなに消費電力が大きいのか
Because the way it does it is like a mobile phone
やり方が携帯電話みたいだから
It's what a computer's mind does
それはコンピューターの頭脳がやることだ
the same phone
同じ電話
you somehow see it
なんとなく見えますね
It's doing it in a bit of an ultra-PC way
ちょっとした超PC的な方法でそれを行っています
OK everyone often says
OK、誰もがよく言います
what you see on your pc right now
今あなたのPCに表示されているもの
Might be on the phone in a while
しばらく電話に出るかもしれない
OK so what I'm going to say is
OK、それで、私が言いたいのは、
Actually this is wrong OK
実はこれは間違いです
We go from A to B like this
こんな感じでAからBまで行きます
it's really fast
本当に速いです
but it's basically
しかしそれは基本的に
The logic of thinking is different
思考のロジックが違う
Because how people use mobile phones
なぜなら、人々は携帯電話をどのように使用するのか
It is different from using a computer
パソコンを使うのとは違います
Not to mention how people use watches
人々が時計をどのように使用するかは言うまでもありません
It's completely different from using a computer
パソコンを使うのとは全く違います
Let me give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
your watch keeps moving
あなたの時計は動き続けます
I think many people have used this smart watch
このスマートウォッチを使ったことがある人も多いと思います
It's not very useful
あまり役に立ちません
I have several of my own and I'm fine
自分のものをいくつか持っていますが、大丈夫です
Because I am doing related research myself, I am using
私自身も関連研究を行っているため、
its interface is difficult to use
インターフェースが使いにくい
Then I'll find something to slide around
そしたら滑れる何かを見つけるよ
Sometimes I can't find what I want
欲しいものが見つからないこともある
Of course the phone is the same
もちろん電話も同じです
But the phone will be better
でも電話の方が良くなるよ
It's at least slightly closer to your computer
あなたのコンピュータに少なくともわずかに近い
So what I'm going to say is
それで、私が言いたいのは、
personal use
個人使用
get used to it
それに慣れる
Must be able to reflect the design of your computer
コンピューターのデザインを反映できる必要があります
Not only in the design of the interface
インターフェースのデザインだけでなく、
and including its operation
そしてその運用も含めて
must be done like this
このようにしなければなりません
say your watch
あなたの時計を言ってください
if you don't pick it up
拾わないと
Actually why do so many things
実際、なぜそんなにたくさんのことをするのですか
Wouldn't it be better if you just timed it?
時間を計ったほうがいいんじゃないでしょうか？
There are actually things to do when you pick it up
実際に手に取ったらやるべきことがある
ok so our
わかりました、それでは私たちの
the way of using the habit of using
使い方、習慣
Of course the system should do this
もちろんシステムはこれを行うべきです
Unfortunately that's not the case now
残念ながら今はそうではありません
ok, why does the phone consume so much power
OK、なぜ電話はそんなに多くの電力を消費するのでしょうか
Why Smartwatch Your iWatch
iWatch をスマートウォッチにする理由
Charge every two days
2日ごとに充電する
because it's not right
それは間違っているから
ok, the future is actually this direction
OK、未来は実際にこの方向にあります
Everyone is thinking about how to do new things
新しいものをどうやって作るかをみんなが考えている
Especially when it comes to the Internet of Things, it should not be done like this
特にモノのインターネットに関しては、このようにすべきではありません
when you go to the doctor
医者に行くとき
Maybe I'll take a bracelet home with me later
後でブレスレットを持って帰るかも
when will you see the doctor next time
次回いつ医者に診てもらえますか
maybe a month from now
おそらく今から一ヶ月後
maybe half a year later
半年後かな
correct can't run out of power
正しい電力を使い果たすことはできません
you go home and ask everyone to take it back
あなたは家に帰り、みんなにそれを持ち帰るように頼みます
Take it off and charge it
取り外して充電してください
Many people don't know how to charge, right?
充電方法がわからない人も多いのでは？
best time to go
行くのに最適な時間
The doctor took a look
医者は診てくれた
give you another one
もう一つあげてください
By the way, put the information in
ちなみに情報を入れますと、
ok, what can last half a year
さて、半年も続くだろうか
Our current watch will never need to change the battery for a lifetime
私たちの現在の時計は一生電池を交換する必要がありません
not dead yet, right?
まだ死んではいないですよね？
You think what I'm going to say is right
あなたは私の言うことが正しいと思っていますか
Now many designs are problematic
現在、多くのデザインが問題を抱えています
So this user interface follows the user's habits
したがって、このユーザーインターフェイスはユーザーの習慣に従っています
real implementation
実際の実装
TALK APP IN DESIGN ON YOUR PHONE
あなたの携帯電話のデザインでトークアプリ
WATCH WEAR ARE ABOVE EVERYTHING
時計の着用はすべてに優先します
that's right
それは正しい
OK this is my first question I think
OK、これが私の最初の質問だと思います
The second question is actually to say
2番目の質問は実際に言うことです
This phone is actually in the process of glasses
この携帯電話は実はメガネ加工中です
only many things it will appear
たくさんのものだけが表示されます
some things will disappear ok
いくつかのものは消えるでしょう、大丈夫
Then I want to talk about the first thing is to say
それから私が話したいのは、最初に言いたいことは、
You see the idea of ​​Android design
Androidのデザインの考え方がわかります
At the bottom of it is an operating system
その一番下にはオペレーティングシステムがあります
A so-called intermediary software is made above
いわゆる仲介ソフトは上記で作られています
It is the FriendWalk layer
FriendWalkレイヤーです
why does it do this
なぜこんなことをするのか
In fact, its purpose is to pull everyone in.
実際、その目的は全員を引き込むことです。
Many things can be placed on this layer
このレイヤーには多くのものを配置できます
A field stuff comes in
畑のものが入ってくる
it made hardware
それはハードウェアを作りました
it has something to put here
ここに置くものがある
Come in on field B
Bフィールドに入ってください
it comes in it stuff can go here
それが入っています ここに物を入れることができます
So he wrapped everyone in this thing
それで彼はみんなをこれで包みました
OK, so everyone is roleplaying
さて、みんなでロールプレイングです
OK let's build this whole ecosystem together
OK、このエコシステム全体を一緒に構築しましょう
OK, so the first thing that comes up
OK、それで最初に思い浮かぶのは
The basic idea is to hope that everyone can play together
基本的な考え方は、みんなで一緒に遊べることを願うことです
OK, so of course what if in the process?
OK、もちろん、その過程にある場合はどうなるでしょうか?
Actually there is no way to avoid it
実際にはそれを避ける方法はありません
A lot of things will leak out because of this.
このせいで色々なものが漏れてしまいます。
because everyone knows what it looks like
それがどのようなものかは誰もが知っているので
OK, let's go back and say
OK、戻って言いましょう
What about data protection? OK
データ保護についてはどうですか? OK
Data Protection is Now in the Cloud Era
データ保護はクラウド時代へ
Everyone's most painful question
誰もが最も痛ましい質問
You all know I went online and searched for that thing
私がネットにアクセスしてそれを検索したことは皆さんご存知でしょう
or after accidentally putting something on it
または誤ってその上に何かを置いた後
I bake shellfish all over the place, right?
貝類をあちこちで焼いているんですよね。
Really can't finish killing, right?
本当に殺しきれないですよね？
I don’t know where the Cache went, right?
キャッシュがどこに行ったのかわかりませんよね？
Google also keeps several copies
Google も複数のコピーを保管しています
I don't know how to get rid of it
取り除く方法がわかりません
You still told him if you could kill me for me, right?
あなたはまだ彼に、私の代わりに私を殺してもらえますかと言ったよね？
that's it
それでおしまい
So actually
それで実際には
Now everyone is starting to think about this question OK
今、誰もがこの質問について考え始めています。
Not just encrypting and decrypting data
データの暗号化と復号化だけではありません
how can it be
どうしてそうなるの
It's easy to permanently erase your data
データを完全に消去するのは簡単です
ok
Ok
So this is the next important job
ということで、これが次の重要な仕事です
This work may not be possible by
この作業は次の方法では実行できない可能性があります
or not just should be used by android like this
それともこのようにAndroidで使用する必要がありますか
such an institution
そのような機関
Or such a platform to do
またはそのようなプラットフォーム
ok this is actually
わかりました、これは実際には
problems everyone has
誰もが抱えている問題
will deal with
対処します
Does he have something permanent
彼は何か永続的なものを持っているのだろうか
don't show us
私たちに見せないでください
ok
Ok
My current experience is
私の現在の経験は、
not so much
それほど多くない
ok
Ok
ourselves on top
自分たちが上にいる
Modified a lot of things
たくさんのことを修正しました
did a lot of research
たくさんの研究をしました
In fact, we can still see
実際、私たちはまだ見ることができます
ok
Ok
Generally no big problem
一般的には大きな問題はありません
but what is the biggest problem
しかし最大の問題は何ですか
the biggest problem is
最大の問題は
Today, for example, a manufacturer
たとえば今日、あるメーカーは、
ok
Ok
He does, for example, image processing
彼はたとえば画像処理を行います
so he has something
それで彼は何かを持っています
he will get involved
彼は巻き込まれるだろう
Modification of some things in the structure
構造内の一部の変更
then you are scary
それならあなたは怖いです
It is not easy for him to understand this
彼にとってこれを理解するのは簡単ではない
how did it move
どうやって動いたのか
ok
Ok
He doesn't want to talk to you
彼はあなたと話したくないのです
So even if that thing is over there
だからたとえそれがあそこにあったとしても
Actually I don't understand
実は分かりません
ok
Ok
This is a
これは
when we do it ourselves
自分たちでやるとき
a problem to face
直面する問題
still have a question
まだ質問があります
that is
あれは
everything today
今日のすべて
Although open source
オープンソースとはいえ、
But this guard against gentlemen is not against villains
しかし、紳士に対するこの警戒は悪党に対するものではない
ok
Ok
That is to say
つまり
I made this thing
こんなものを作りました
I will open source though
でもオープンソースにするよ
show everyone
みんなに見せて
I can be half a year late
半年遅れてもいいよ
I'll give it to you later
後であげます
procrastinating
先延ばしにする
ok
Ok
You can't get the latest version if you want to get something
何かを入手したくても最新バージョンを入手できない
like these soft hard ways
このようなソフトでハードな方法のように
we all have some degree
私たちは皆、ある程度の学位を持っています
Come
来て
Delay
遅れ
get this thing out
これを出しなさい
But what?
でも何？
In terms of openness
開放性という意味では
exist
存在
on android
アンドロイドで
We haven't had too many problems
あまり問題は起きていない
ok
Ok
big problem
大問題
In fact, it should be in
実際には、それは次のとおりである必要があります
this other compare
この他の比較
mid-walled
中壁
make a system inside
内部にシステムを作る
Those things are less available
そういったものは入手可能性が低くなります
ask the director what to do
ディレクターにどうするかを聞く
Prevent VIP Groups
VIP グループの防止
when we use that computer
私たちがそのコンピューターを使うとき
For mobile phones all the time
いつでも携帯電話に
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
The best way is to copy
最良の方法はコピーすることです
ensure safety
確保安全
copy
コピー
copy things
物をコピーする
then hide it
それからそれを隠します
OK
OK
this is the best way
これが最良の方法です
because i'm serious
私は真剣だから
Because everything can be hacked
あらゆるものがハッキングされる可能性があるため、
OK
OK
The only thing that can't be broken is that you put the copy in your luggage
壊れない唯一のものは、コピーを荷物の中に入れることです
I'm not kidding
冗談じゃないよ
like my own practice is
私自身の練習のように
I copied it to the hard drive after a while
しばらくしてからハードディスクにコピーしました
I put it away if it's important
大事なものなら置いておきます
OK
OK
That
それか
people can't get it
人々はそれを得ることができない
OK
OK
Be sure to install antivirus software.
必ずウイルス対策ソフトウェアをインストールしてください。
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
I have a
私は持っています
doubt gold
金を疑う
Now data science is actually quite popular, and there are many opportunities
現在、データサイエンスは実際に非常に人気があり、多くの機会があります
Compared with this service fee, there is no boundary between people
このサービス料金に比べれば、人と人の境界はありません
And always filled with more sprites
そしていつもより多くのスプライトで満たされています
But compared to the other part of the feeling
しかし、他の部分の感情と比較すると、
Even on the opposite side of Xianxue, there may be some threats
Xianxueの反対側にも脅威が存在する可能性があります
Have these threats slowly turned into trends?
こうした脅威は徐々にトレンドになってきたのでしょうか?
It may even subvert the current ecology in the future
将来的には現在の生態系を破壊する可能性さえある
Have you ever thought about which of these things may have a better chance of affecting our entire life?
これらのうちどれが私たちの人生全体に影響を与える可能性が高いか考えたことがありますか?
Now this eCos etc.
さてこのエコスなど。
In fact, you just mentioned this and immediately thought of the safety mentioned by the doctor just now.
実は、今おっしゃって、今先生がおっしゃった安全性というのがすぐに思い浮かんだんです。
Security can be disrupted
セキュリティが混乱する可能性がある
Somewhat subversive cloud computing
やや破壊的なクラウド コンピューティング
Because you are afraid of leaking a lot of information.
多くの情報が漏洩することを恐れているからです。
After you put it on, if something is not safe, you are very scared
履いた後に危険なものがあったら怖いですよね
At this time, it will affect everyone to use the shared storage space
現時点では、共有ストレージスペースを全員が使用することに影響します
So everyone feels unsafe
だから誰もが危険を感じる
the first point
最初の点
Second point
2点目
I give an example
例を挙げます
like myself using this search engine
私のようにこの検索エンジンを使用しています
Or when using the so-called browser
またはいわゆるブラウザを使用する場合
In fact, you also said that I have a bit of this
実際、あなたは私にもこれが少しあるとも言いました
paranoia of persecution
被迫害妄想症
OK
OK
I have several browsers
いくつかのブラウザを持っています
Actually, I don't always use one
実はいつも使っているわけではないのですが、
sometimes
時々
Use Firefox sometimes Chrome I sometimes use IE when I'm happy
時々 Firefox を使います Chrome 楽しいときは時々 IE を使います
because
なぜなら
I don't want people to know too much
あまり人に知られたくない
why do i tell him so many things
なぜ私は彼にそんなにたくさんのことを言うのですか
OK
OK
Are you afraid that someone is watching you from behind?
誰かが後ろから見ているのが怖いですか？
When Google Knows Everything
Google がすべてを知っているとき
he can sell you too
彼もあなたを売ることができます
OK
OK
After he can analyze it one day
いつか分析できたら
Tell you like the Minority Report
マイノリティ・リポートが好きだと伝えてください
ah you
ああ、あなた
what might happen
何が起こるかもしれない
OK can you?
いいですか？
He knows you're dangerous after too many things
彼はあなたが色々なことをしすぎると危険になることを知っています
OK he knows the water in your house is water
OK、彼はあなたの家の水が水であることを知っています
OK, I know where you're flying to today
OK、今日どこへ飛ぶか知っています
Can he guarantee that your information will not be stolen by others?
あなたの情報が他人に盗まれないことを彼は保証できますか?
It's actually hard
実際は難しいです
Very difficult
非常に難しい
OK so I think
OK、そう思います
When you ask this question, my first thought is safety
この質問をされたとき、私が最初に考えるのは安全性です
OK Data Security
OK 資料的安全
my second thought was
私の2番目の考えは
I don't want a Big Brother watching me from behind
ビッグブラザーに後ろから見られたくない
he knows everything ok
彼はすべてを知っています
Sometimes it's hard to think about
時々考えるのが難しいことがある
Although he can't do anything
彼は何も出来ないのに
I'm not afraid of him knowing
彼が知っても怖くない
but weird
でも変だ
I'm afraid he knows everything
残念ながら彼はすべてを知っている
I immediately thought of these two things
すぐに思いついたのはこの2つ
This may cause some problems for our cloud computing
これにより、クラウド コンピューティングに問題が発生する可能性があります。
Of course you can look at it from another angle
もちろん別角度からも見ることができます
For example, cloud computing
たとえば、クラウドコンピューティング
Would you say it's good for Taiwan?
それは台湾にとって良いことだと思いますか？
yet another question
さらに別の質問
OK
OK
You say we sell machines
私たちは機械を売っていると言いましたね
We used to sell a lot of machines
昔は機械もたくさん売ってた
Everybody sell us machines
みんな機械を売ってくれます
Now many people don't sell us machines
今では多くの人が私たちに機械を売ってくれません
he rents the machine
彼はその機械を借ります
Are our machines sold less
私たちの機械は売れなくなっていますか
OK
OK
so you can look at it from different angles
さまざまな角度から見ることができるので、
Actually, is it good for us?
実際、それは私たちにとって良いことなのでしょうか？
in this process
この過程で
Actually we also lost
実は私たちも負けてしまいました
quite a lot
かなりたくさん
in this wave
この波の中で
what did we catch
私たちは何を捕まえましたか
Of course it's worth it
もちろんそれだけの価値はあります
look at it from another angle
別の角度から見てください
what the hell is going on
一体何が起こっているのか
I may not have fully answered your question
あなたの質問に完全には答えていないかもしれません
But the first thing to think about is safety
しかし、最初に考えるべきことは安全性です
It's not safe and I don't want to put things on it
安全ではないので、その上に物を置きたくない
hello thank you for your wonderful speech
こんにちは、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとう
Speaking of Information Security
情報セキュリティといえば
it must be said
それは言わなければなりません
Actually this time Apple
実は今回はアップル
impossible to open it that
それを開けるのは不可能です
World of Terrorist Attacks
テロ攻撃の世界
Of course it can take a long time
もちろん長い時間がかかることもあります
i want to ask
聞きたいです
You develop a research scholar's perspective on a hierarchy system
階層システム開発に関する研究者の視点
how do you look at this problem
この問題をどう見ていますか
From our point of view
私たちの観点からすると
If we have a way we want to break see
打ち破りたい方法があるなら見てください
Let's see if we can do it
できるかどうかやってみよう
This of course means
これはもちろん意味します
From the point of view of a researcher
研究者の視点から
Of course we would like to know about this
もちろん、私たちはこれについて知りたいと思っています
If you look at it from the perspective of providing a platform
プラットフォームを提供するという観点から見ると
Then do you feel that it is safe for you to use his system?
それでは、彼のシステムを使用するのは安全だと思いますか?
But of course it's like what you said
でも確かにあなたの言う通りですね
there's a lot to debate
議論すべきことはたくさんある
Should a manufacturer do this?
メーカーはこれを行う必要がありますか？
I think this may have a lot of views
たぶん閲覧数が多いと思います
That's actually from my own
それは実際に私自身からのものです
From my own research point of view
私自身の研究の観点から
I actually often want to know
実はよく知りたいのですが
Did this manufacturer leave a back door?
このメーカーはバックドアを残しましたか？
after he left the back door
彼が裏口から出た後
He can do many great things
彼はたくさんの素晴らしいことができる
i don't like what he does
彼のやることは好きではない
OK
OK
I would also guess that
私もそう推測します
Later he said he could
後で彼はできると言った
I knew he had a back door
彼には裏口があることは知っていた
OK
OK
Well of course there aren't many here
まあもちろん数は多くないけど
I think of many things myself
自分でも色々なことを考えます
OK
OK
but
しかし
basically i think
基本的に私は思う
from this
これから
Apple he refuses to help with this
Apple、これに関して協力を拒否
FBI
FBI
From the point of view of doing this
これをやるという観点から見ると
actually
実際
from our system
私たちのシステムから
From a development point of view
開発の観点から見ると
actually i think
実際私は思う
many things can be broken
多くのものが壊れる可能性があります
OK
OK
but do you know
でも知っていますか
how to break it
それをどうやって壊すか
as if you have seen
まるで見たかのように
Turin this movie
トリノのこの映画
oh ron fishing
ああロン 釣りん
during World War II
第二次世界大戦中
Break the German code
ドイツの暗号を解読する
It stands to reason that the encryption cannot be broken.
暗号化を解読できないのは当然です。
but why broke
でもなぜ壊れたのか
because he knows some rules
彼はいくつかのルールを知っているので
every time he was in the german army
彼がドイツ軍にいたときはいつも
when someone is delivering something
誰かが何かを配達しているとき
I sent some words on it before
前にそれについていくつかの言葉を送りました
so he knows
だから彼は知っている
relationship with that thing
その物との関係
He because of this relationship
彼はこの関係のせいで
He cracks what's behind
彼は背後にあるものを分解します
So something theoretically unsolvable
理論的には解決不可能なこと
In fact, it is actually solvable
実はそれは解決できるんです
Back to this phone from Apple
Apple からこの携帯電話に戻る
In fact, there are some secrets inside if you know
実は、知れば知るほど内部には秘密があるのです
Why can't it be broken?
なぜ壊れないのでしょうか？
must be broken
壊れなければなりません
just didn't know it had some secrets in it
それにはいくつかの秘密があることを知りませんでした
How does it do?
それはどのように行われるのでしょうか？
so everything can break
だからすべてが壊れる可能性がある
i think
私が思うに
As long as things made by people can be broken
人が作ったものが壊れる限り
It's just that I don't know the secret
ただその秘密が分からないだけです
Ask Mr. Guo
郭さんに聞く
Just mentioned Taiwan and information companies
先ほど台湾と情報企業について触れました
It's not as good as before the bright moon in the world
世界に明るい月が現れる前ほどではない
So what is the main reason?
では、主な理由は何でしょうか?
So what do you think is the solution?
それで、解決策は何だと思いますか？
Thanks
ありがとう
Actually, I'm not in charge of security.
実は私はセキュリティ担当ではありません。
I saw this and I thought
これを見て思った
Wow how we are so honorable OK
うわー、私たちはとても光栄です、OK
we are actually one
私たちは実際には一つです
A good place to do information security research
情報セキュリティの研究を行うのに最適な場所
OK
OK
It's not just that there are many people on the other side wanting to hack our website
向こう側に私たちのウェブサイトをハッキングしようとしている人がたくさんいるというだけではありません
Naturally, another big issue is
当然のことながら、もう一つ大きな問題があります。
In fact, in our environment
実際、私たちの環境では
In fact, everyone doesn't pay much attention to law and order.
実際、誰もが法と秩序にあまり注意を払っていません。
i ask a question
質問をする
How many people have anti-virus software installed on their mobile phones
携帯電話にウイルス対策ソフトウェアをインストールしている人は何人いますか
Have it
それを持っている
don't feel bad
悪く思わないでください
Because I didn't even pretend to be OK
平気なふりさえしなかったから
In fact, many of us don't pay much attention to it.
実際、私たちの多くはそれにあまり注意を払っていません。
OK so I think it has something to do with our culture too
OK、それは私たちの文化にも関係があると思います
OK, it has something to do with our special environment
OK、それは私たちの特殊な環境に関係があります
OK, so it’s easy for everyone to take us as a springboard to work on it
わかりました。誰もが私たちを踏み台にして取り組むのは簡単です
OK so this is
はい、これです
This is what we have to be careful about
これは私たちが気をつけなければならないことです
Like I said, I talked about it for a long time, whether I am safe or not, I am not safe either
さっきも言ったように、私は長い間それについて話しました、私が安全かどうかは別として、私も安全ではありません
It's Teacher Guo
郭先生です
yes
はい
Mr. Guo
郭さん
i want to ask
聞きたいです
Google the company
会社をグーグルで検索する
because I think it's a
だと思うから
That is a lot of companies
それは多くの企業です
every company
あらゆる企業
Google
グーグル
OK
OK
because when i knew him
なぜなら私が彼を知ったとき
is that his Google community is very strong
それは、彼の Google コミュニティが非常に強力であるということです
then we started to feel
それから私たちは感じ始めました
Gmail works great
Gmail はうまく機能します
then follow him to
それから彼に従ってください
When I start using Gmail
Gmail を使い始めると
He started rolling out Google Maps
彼は Google マップの展開を開始しました
Then his map is very powerful
それから彼の地図は非常に強力です
then that time
それからその時
almost the same
ほぼ同じ
Self-Fone
セルフフォン
social system
社会システム
when starting to upgrade
アップグレードを開始するとき
Then it later became a plus operating system
その後、プラスのオペレーティング システムになりました
Then hit the Microsoft
それからマイクロソフトに問い合わせてください
Just because when he was PC was the beginning
彼がPCだった頃が始まりだったから
Sample reduction
サンプルの削減
and now
そしていま
I found out that he started a business as a stationery car
文具車として起業したことを知りました
that feeling says
その気持ちが言うのは
he is a very
彼はとても
many oriented companies
多くの志向性のある企業
Because he is not like other
彼は他の人とは違うから
How Intel
インテルの仕組み
he wants other companies
彼は他の会社を望んでいます
Just focus on doing this thing
ただこのことをすることに集中してください
And then and he's basically this
そして、彼は基本的にこれです
he is in this generation
彼はこの世代にいる
and our information engineering
そして私たちの情報工学
is a big change
大きな変化です
whole society
社会全体
talk to us some what way
どういう形で私たちに話してください
That
それか
i never get it
決して分かりません
what is he like
彼はどういう感じ
company of
の会社
Why did he so early
なぜ彼はそんなに早くなったのか
Swipe ink to make a map
スワイプして地図を作成する
And how do you think he will change our lives in the future?
そして、彼は将来私たちの生活をどのように変えると思いますか？
OK thank you
わかりました、ありがとう
Actually I don't know many things
実は知らないことが多いんです
If you know I'm rich too, OK
私も金持ちだと知っているなら、OK
Actually, to be honest, it's true.
実際、正直に言えば、それは本当です。
When I first saw Google Map
初めてグーグルマップを見たとき
Actually, I didn't realize it at first
実は最初は気づかなかったのですが、
So many things can be done on it
非常に多くのことができる
including you can do this
あなたも含めてこれができます
Include your search in this region
この地域で検索を含めてください
restaurant, many things
レストラン、いろいろ
There is no way, I immediately think of a lot of work OK
仕方ない、すぐに仕事がたくさん頭に浮かぶ OK
What about when he has a map in his hands and starts navigating?
彼が地図を手に持って航海を始めたときはどうでしょうか?
Actually didn't think of it
実際には考えていませんでした
At that time, it didn't occur to me that he was going to get a car.
その時は、彼が車を買うとは思いもしませんでした。
OK
OK
So this thing is actually
それで、これは実際には
I think these companies are actually very powerful.
これらの企業は実際に非常に強力だと思います。
Because these companies can actually guide
これらの企業は実際に指導できるからです
it can provide great creativity
それは素晴らしい創造性をもたらすことができます
This is actually
これは実際には
i want to be like everyone
私はみんなのようになりたいです
It is also observed that there are several very special companies
非常に特殊な企業がいくつかあることも観察されています。
Not just Google but companies like Amazon
GoogleだけでなくAmazonのような企業も
Or you have seen several
あるいは、いくつか見たことがある
Including companies like Tesla
テスラのような企業も含まれる
In fact, they are all shaping and changing our world
実際、それらはすべて私たちの世界を形成し、変えています
Without companies like Google
Googleのような企業がなければ
In fact, Cloud computing will not be what it is now
実際、クラウド コンピューティングは今のようなものではなくなるでしょう
If there were no companies like Amazon
もしアマゾンのような企業がなかったら
In fact, there are many things that are good for shopping
実は買い物に便利なものがたくさんあるんです
Or even these so-called platforms rent these
あるいは、これらのいわゆるプラットフォームでさえ、これらをレンタルしています
won't go to these places
これらの場所には行きません
Of course you can also say that the time has just come
もちろん、その時期が来たとも言えます。
But their process of leading the world and bringing these ideas
しかし、彼らが世界をリードし、これらのアイデアをもたらしたプロセス
It's actually pretty amazing
実はかなりすごいんです
I find it amazing
すごいと思います
Then what do you say you will go when you come down?
じゃあ、降りてきたら何に行くって言うの？
In fact, of course you all know that
実は皆さんももちろんご存知のことですが、
Coming down must be towards this very soon
降下はもうすぐこの方向に向かうはずだ
Everyone, when you see the car, it must appear immediately.
皆さん、車を見たらすぐに現れるはずです。
That wearable thing is also emerging
あのウェアラブルなものも登場
these things will change soon
これらのことはすぐに変わります
Of course there are many things that will come out
もちろん出てくるものもたくさんありますが、
So the robot stuff is pretty fast I guess
ロボット関連はかなり速いと思います
these things are very fast
これらは非常に速いです
You see Google spends a lot of money doing this stuff
Google がこのことに多額の資金を費やしていることがわかります
His demo robot last time was actually very powerful
前回の彼のデモロボットは実際非常に強力でした
The robot can actually be in such an unstable state
ロボットは実際にこのような不安定な状態になる可能性があります
can walk
歩ける
that was difficult
それは難しかった
that was very difficult
それはとても難しかったです
Walking on snow is actually far south of walking on such ground
雪の上を歩くことは、実際にはそのような地面を歩くことよりはるかに南です
it's very difficult
とても難しい
So I don't really know what else he's going to do.
だから彼が他に何をするつもりなのかは本当に分かりません。
If so, you tell me I've bought his stock
もしそうなら、私が彼の株を買ったと教えてください
Thanks
ありがとう
Director Guo here
郭監督はこちら
i ask two questions
2つの質問をします
The first is safety and the other is economy
1 つは安全性、もう 1 つは経済性です
In fact, many safe places are over-proportioned.
実際、安全な場所の多くは過剰な割合を占めています。
In fact, for example, technology has brought many good things
実際、例えばテクノロジーは多くの良いことをもたらしました。
I am doing information myself.
私自身も情報発信を行っています。
From MapFriend to Mobile
MapFriendからモバイルへ
There may be fewer mobile phones in the future
将来的には携帯電話の台数が減るかもしれない
attached to the body attached to the body
ボディに取り付けられています ボディに取り付けられています
One scene is simply your ID authentication is your ears
ワンシーンはあなたのID認証があなたの耳になるだけです
your face
あなたの顔
you can use it as a certification
証明書として使用できます
The presence of mobile phones is sometimes even more
携帯電話の存在は時にはさらに大きくなります
will gradually decrease
徐々に減っていきます
This time an area actually
今回は実際にあるエリア
security fact
安全上の事実
There are two levels of security we're talking about
私たちが話しているセキュリティには 2 つのレベルがあります
a national level
全国レベルの
a personal level
個人レベル
In fact, most of you now are at the national level
実際、皆さんのほとんどは現在国家レベルにいます。
That's because we have worked hard for many years
それは私たちが長年頑張ってきたからです
For example, IP Oracle
たとえば、IP オラクル
its database
そのデータベース
charge you a lot of money
多額のお金を請求する
We pay Microsoft every day
私たちはマイクロソフトに毎日支払いをしています
Now that Free Software comes out
フリーソフトウェアが出てきた今、
Of course you are cheaper
もちろん安いですよ
In fact we are being tried
実際、私たちは試されている
they are landlords
彼らは家主です
we are computers
私たちはコンピューターです
Write software on it every day
毎日そこにソフトウェアを書き込む
That day Free Software came out
フリーソフトウェアが登場したその日
The other landlord came out again
他の家主がまた出てきた
then what i want to say is
それから私が言いたいのは
Actually the thing to say is something like
実際に言うべきことは次のようなものです
after it comes out
それが出た後
The certified part of its NXRP
NXRP の認定部分
Its entire mechanism has been disengaged
そのメカニズム全体が解除されました
Credit Mechanism of Visit Master
ビジットマスターのクレジットの仕組み
Part of its front NXRP
フロントNXRPの一部
It's another mechanism
それは別の仕組みです
Therefore, our credit basis will be based on the credit basis of payment in the future.
したがって、今後の支払いは信用基準に基づいて行われます。
Built in the CCP's database
中国共産党のデータベースに組み込まれている
So your safety I'll give you another example is to say
あなたの安全のために、別の例を挙げます。
In fact, tens of millions of dollars are stolen from our bank every year during the Chinese New Year. Everyone doesn’t know.
実際、毎年旧正月に私たちの銀行から数千万ドルが盗まれていますが、誰も知りません。
Then put it on to deal with it, and everyone will cover it
それからそれに対処するためにそれを着てください、そうすれば皆がそれをカバーします
So every day in a safe and unsafe environment, you can actually make backups
つまり、安全な環境でも危険な環境でも、毎日実際にバックアップを作成できます。
People steal things you want to see, you can definitely see them
君が見たいものを人は盗む、君には必ず見える
It's just whether he's driving to see, so it's a matter of safety.
それは彼が運転して見に行くかどうかだけなので、それは安全の問題です。
Considering so much when someone steals information like yours from our Dao Ke
誰かが私たちの道科からあなたのような情報を盗んだとき、とても考えます
Or how to cheat, many technologies will be damaged
あるいは不正行為を行うと多くの技術がダメージを受けることになる
I must say that when this original list comes out, it will hurt him
このオリジナルのリストが出てきたら、彼は傷つくだろうと言わざるを得ません。
But he has a part, some people do anti-virus, and some people
でも彼にも役割はある、ウイルス対策に携わる人もいるし、人もいる
For example, in terms of anti-virus, maybe he is the one who releases poison, so it is 360 degrees
例えばウイルス対策で言えば毒を出す人かもしれないので360度です。
We used above, for example, he made Lag or something
たとえば、上で使用したように、彼はラグか何かを作成しました
So there is a good side and a bad side
だから良い面もあれば悪い面もある
I really talked about some V numbers, just like I watch VR and AR
VRやARを見るのと同じように、いくつかのVナンバーについて本当に話しました
It seems to be the same as the power storage
本物の蓄電器と同じみたいですね
So, I think personal safety is still
したがって、個人の安全は依然として確保されていると思います
Some people do it safely while others do it unsafely
安全に行う人もいれば、危険に行う人もいます
Both will change
どっちも変わるよ
So you may be afraid of too many things and become love instead
だからあなたはあまりにも多くのことを恐れて、代わりに愛になるかもしれません
Like our own information security
私たち自身の情報セキュリティと同様に
America doesn't speak that many words yet
アメリカはまだそれほど多くの言葉を話していない
When you go to Taiwan, you have to ask questions about what to say.
台湾に行くと何を話すべきか質問しなければなりません。
Ask three passwords for everything
すべてに 3 つのパスワードを要求する
I said my home address
自宅の住所を言いました
It's sign 116
サイン116です
That's a T
それはTです
All questions annoy him
すべての質問が彼をイライラさせる
A lot of information security has been overdone
多くの情報セキュリティが過剰になっている
People want to see your things and want to harm your things
人々はあなたのものを見たい、あなたのものに害を与えたいと思っています
Didn't say I can't get it
手に入らないとは言ってない
It's just too late for him to make a move
彼が行動を起こすには遅すぎる
I want to talk about safety or something
安全性などについて話したいのですが
I talk about economic issues
経済問題について話します
In fact, Ma Yun's problem has brought
実際、馬雲の問題は
He sucks 450 billion a day
彼は一日に4500億を吸います
He should be able to cope with it in six months
彼は半年以内にはそれに対処できるはずだ
The whole world is sucking him away
全世界が彼を吸い取っている
Ma Yun is a wolf who offered soldiers and said he was a disaster
馬雲は兵士を差し出す狼で、自分は災難だと言った
OK, the Chinese Communist Party is also guarding against it now.
そうですね、中国共産党も今は警戒しています。
In fact, it has brought about 30% to 50% of the bank
実際、それは銀行の約 30% ～ 50% をもたらしました。
Will not exist in the future will be dumped
将来的には存在しないでしょう
The bank is not that big in the office
オフィス内にある銀行はそれほど大きくありません
blow air conditioner a lot of sailors
たくさんの船員がエアコンを吹く
it will become a small office
小さなオフィスになります
So what I'm going to talk about is
それで、私が話そうとしているのは、
A lot of manpower is released
大量の人員が解放される
Last year, the channel brought about one million stores in mainland China
昨年、このチャネルは中国本土に約 100 万店舗をもたらしました
Not on the big market, on the middle market
大きな市場ではなく中間市場で
So the problem in the future is a polarized problem
したがって、将来の問題は二極化した問題になります
rich people are rich
金持ちは金持ちだ
no money is no money
お金がないのはお金がない
So from twenty two you can have
22 時からは、
There are so many careers to find a job
仕事を見つけるにはたくさんのキャリアがあります
Almost everything below is doing building work
以下のほとんどすべてが建設作業を行っています
The middle is all braked
真ん中は全部ブレーキかかってる
Replace all three words
3 つの単語すべてを置き換えます
Whether traffic braking
交通ブレーキかどうか
Foley Brake Chemicals
フォーリーブレーキケミカル
almost no one is there
ほとんど誰もいない
Then the economic problem at this time
それから今回の経済問題は
There is a problem of decoupling from the currency
通貨とのデカップリングの問題がある
that capital is rich
その資本は豊かです
For example, today I met a
たとえば、今日私はある人に会いました。
For example, today we do venture capital
たとえば、今日私たちはベンチャーキャピタルを行っています。
I haven't had a day
一日も持たなかった
There are 20 households losing 5 million each
20世帯がそれぞれ500万を失っている
I am the major shareholder of each
私はそれぞれの主要株主です
Then account for those VC
次に、それらの VC について説明します
What is the bed Startup Brainpower
ベッドとは Start Brain Power
The start-up is working under the account
スタートアップはそのアカウントで動作しています
Then he always takes the most money
そうするといつも彼が一番お金を取ります
Therefore, in the future, the relationship between the United States and the CCP
したがって、将来的に米国と中国共産党は、
They have money and shout more at the top
彼らは金を持っていて、もっと上で叫ぶんだ
I think we have a problem with the problem
問題に問題があると思います
In fact, it means
実際、それが意味するのは、
The economy will bring about the next
経済は次のことをもたらす
The next phase of the revolution
革命の次の段階
what's your opinion
あなたの意見は何ですか
Because in fact too many careers
実際にはキャリアが多すぎるため、
Too many poor people are enslaved
あまりにも多くの貧しい人々が奴隷にされている
Two phases
2段階
This time the power of the times is actually a rebound
今度は時代の力が実は反動で
Then this must be an economic issue
となると、これは経済的な問題に違いない
more dangerous
もっと危ない
Thanks
ありがとう
I think indeed
確かにそう思います
this new economic era
この新しい経済時代
New technology will definitely bring about new changes
新しいテクノロジーは必ず新しい変化をもたらす
This is for sure
これは確かです
ok
Ok
What about the process?
プロセスについてはどうですか？
In fact, as we just mentioned
実際、先ほども述べたように、
something will disappear
何かが消えるだろう
some will appear
いくつかは表示されます
ok
Ok
that as
それは
From the perspective of this research
この研究の観点から見ると
or from an educational point of view
あるいは教育的な観点から
In fact, we have to get used to these things very quickly.
実際、私たちはこれらのことにすぐに慣れる必要があります。
know what the future might hold
将来何が起こるかを知る
OK
OK
How can we bring our students
どうすれば生徒を連れていけるのか
And bring to our society the public
そして私たちの社会にもたらすもの
what a warning
なんという危険信号だ
or what should be done in research
あるいは研究で何をすべきか
I think it's hard to do
やるのは難しいと思います
OK
OK
And this thing is international now
そしてこれは今や国際的です
The problem is actually very, very complicated
問題は実際には非常に非常に複雑です
I also agree
私も同意します
In fact, you can't be afraid of everything
実際、すべてを恐れることはできない
If you say you want to be completely 100% safe
完全に100%安全でありたいと言うなら
It is actually difficult
実際には難しいです
It is always a principle of proportion
それは常に比例の原則です
where can it be done
どこでできますか
you think it's ok
あなたは大丈夫だと思いますか
where should it be done
どこでやるべきか
Some places may adopt a more conservative approach
場所によっては、より保守的なアプローチを採用する場合があります
some places may compare
いくつかの場所は比較するかもしれません
the money
お金
This compares to the previous one
前回と比べてみるとこれ
Don't think about these things compare this
こういうことは考えないでください、これと比べてください
can't talk about money
お金のことは話せない
It's basically a way of pushing forward
基本的には前に進む方法です
In fact, there are different strategies in it.
実際、そこにはさまざまな戦略が含まれています。
so i agree
だから私は同意します
There is a consideration like
のような考察があります
good
良い
I think it's almost time
そろそろ時間だと思う
Thank you so much today
今日は本当にありがとうございました
My master's wonderful speech
師匠の素晴らしいスピーチ